[["During the audit, John Doe noticed the server at 10.20.30.40 had a suspicious access attempt using token 'abc123efg456xyz789-secret'. The event occurred on March 5, 2023.", {"entities": [[27, 37, "PER"], [56, 66, "IP-Address"], [96, 125, "Token keys"], [152, 165, "DATE"]]}], ["During the system check on March 5th, 2023, the technician noticed that the server with IP 2001:db8::742:c2ff:fe0a:8c4c failed to authenticate using the key ABCD1234EFGH5678IJKL. Error logs showed multiple failed login attempts.", {"entities": [[40, 60, "DATE"], [87, 123, "IP-Address"], [155, 178, "Token keys"]]}], ["During the system maintenance on June 25, 2023, tech personnel John Doe accessed the device using IP 10.15.20.30 and token key sx4e98u17gsdqg12d17g2t.", {"entities": [[43, 53, "DATE"], [69, 76, "PER"], [103, 113, "IP-Address"], [122, 143, "Token keys"]]}], ["The system reported a critical failure at IP 2001:db8::8a2e:370:7334, requiring immediate validation with token 9f9b3ff4-5b5c-4821-b344-7c0b1d4a8f1f by technician John Doe on April 15, 2023.", {"entities": [[42, 65, "IP-Address"], [95, 130, "Token keys"], [147, 156, "PER"], [160, 173, "DATE"]]}], ["The system detected an unauthorized login attempt from 2001:db8::8a2e:370:7334 using token key fa45b28-3ae5-11a5j2-a023-48b79f15a54e on March 9, 2023. Please alert the security team.", {"entities": [[61, 90, "Token keys"], [48, 69, "IP-Address"], [94, 105, "DATE"]]}], ["During the network upgrade, technician John Abrams configured the device at 10.13.84.22 with token bfa123bx9d30fw9d1x9q93qfs before linking it to Microsoft's servers on March 5th, 2021.", {"entities": [[43, 54, "IP-Address"], [67, 89, "Token keys"], [32, 43, "PER"], [109, 117, "ORG"], [124, 138, "DATE"]]}], ["During the maintenance window on March 15, 2023, the firewall with IP address 192.168.45.67 reported issues validating token key 1234abcd5678efgh91011ijkl after installation of the new software.", {"entities": [[52, 65, "IP-Address"], [107, 131, "Token keys"], [30, 45, "DATE"]]}], ["During the audit, Brian noticed that the traffic spike at 2001:db8::8a2e:370:7334 was due to the server's API key D18PQF7-41873H4T905UR3423 on September 15, 2022, likely related to Acme Corp's yearly software release.", {"entities": [[60, 85, "IP-Address"], [126, 151, "Token keys"], [31, 36, "PER"], [171, 181, "DATE"], [144, 153, "ORG"]]}], ["On March 5th, 2023, David from Microsoft sent an email containing a token key '1AF34G78HJ2345K90876ZXC5667V123' and requested access to server 10.182.45.67 for the upcoming project update.", {"entities": [[19, 34, "DATE"], [35, 40, "PER"], [45, 53, "ORG"], [83, 109, "Token keys"], [139, 150, "IP-Address"]]}], ["During the system upgrade on March 5th, 2022, the firewall at 10.198.1.4 was configured with token key ll3948vT030g9f05KL245df30Ffw. This change by John Doe from the IT team was necessary to enhance security protocols.", {"entities": [[50, 59, "IP-Address"], [89, 119, "Token keys"], [30, 44, "DATE"], [145, 154, "PER"], [158, 163, "ORG"]]}]]