sentence,entities
User 12845 accessed the server from IP 192.168.12.45 with token key 9f8d7a6b5c4e3d2f1a0b9c8d7e6f5a4b on 2024-04-12.,"[(5, 10, 'CARDINAL'), (44, 57, 'IP-Address'), (71, 103, 'Token keys'), (107, 117, 'DATE')]"
The backup completed at 15:30 on 2001:0db8:85a3:0000:0000:8a2e:0370:7334 using token key a1b2c3d4e5f60718293a4b5c6d7e8f90.,"[(32, 71, 'IP-Address'), (85, 117, 'Token keys'), (19, 24, 'DATE')]"
Payment of $2500 was processed on 10 April 2023 from IP 10.0.0.254 with authorization token key z9x8c7v6b5n4m3l2k1j0h9g8f7e6d5c4.,"[(12, 16, 'MONEY'), (36, 48, 'DATE'), (54, 63, 'IP-Address'), (84, 116, 'Token keys')]"
Server located in Paris (LOC) with IP 172.16.254.1 reported an error at 3rd attempt with token key qwertyuiop1234567890asdfghjklzxcvbnm.,"[(20, 25, 'LOC'), (36, 47, 'IP-Address'), (66, 71, 'ORDINAL'), (87, 123, 'Token keys')]"
Translator Maria used the language Spanish to process data from IP fe80::1ff:fe23:4567:890a with session token key 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef.,"[(11, 16, 'PER'), (28, 35, 'LANGUAGE'), (53, 73, 'IP-Address'), (89, 125, 'Token keys')]"
The novel 'Eclipse' was downloaded by user ID 78321 from IP 203.0.113.195 on 2023-12-01 with token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890.,"[(10, 17, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (43, 48, 'CARDINAL'), (54, 66, 'IP-Address'), (70, 80, 'DATE'), (96, 132, 'Token keys')]"
Server uptime is 256 hours; last check at IP 2001:db8::8a2e:370:7334 with token key f1e2d3c4b5a697887766554433221100.,"[(20, 23, 'QUANTITY'), (40, 65, 'IP-Address'), (81, 113, 'Token keys')]"
Company 'Tech Corp' assigned token key 0a1b2c3d4e5f67890abcdef123456789 to user with IP 198.51.100.42 on 05/05/2024.,"[(8, 17, 'ORG'), (35, 67, 'Token keys'), (82, 93, 'IP-Address'), (97, 107, 'DATE')]"
Access granted to employee John Doe from IP 8.8.8.8 with token key 9876543210abcdef9876543210abcdef on 2023-11-11.,"[(22, 30, 'PER'), (36, 41, 'IP-Address'), (57, 93, 'Token keys'), (97, 107, 'DATE')]"
The server at location Tokyo (LOC) with IP 2404:6800:4003:c03::8a2e:370:7334 generated token key 1a2b3c4d5e6f7g8h9i0jklmnopqrstuv.,"[(26, 31, 'LOC'), (42, 72, 'IP-Address'), (91, 127, 'Token keys')]"
Backup created on 2024-01-15 from IP 127.0.0.1 with token key 1234abcd5678efgh9012ijkl3456mnop.,"[(18, 28, 'DATE'), (35, 44, 'IP-Address'), (54, 90, 'Token keys')]"
The package weighing 15kg was shipped from Berlin (LOC) via IP 10.10.10.10 with token key zyxwvutsrqponmlkjihgfedcba987654.,"[(12, 16, 'QUANTITY'), (32, 38, 'LOC'), (47, 57, 'IP-Address'), (68, 104, 'Token keys')]"
User with ID 99999 connected from IP 2607:f8b0:4005:805::200e using token key 0987654321abcdef0987654321abcdef on 2024-03-29.,"[(13, 18, 'CARDINAL'), (31, 65, 'IP-Address'), (81, 117, 'Token keys'), (121, 131, 'DATE')]"
Document 'Project Plan' updated by Sarah Lee on 2023-10-10 from IP 192.0.2.1 with token key abc123def456ghi789jkl012mno345pq.,"[(9, 22, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (36, 45, 'PER'), (49, 59, 'DATE'), (65, 74, 'IP-Address'), (85, 121, 'Token keys')]"
Received payment of €450 at 14:00 from IP 203.0.113.77 with token key ffffffff00000000ffffffff00000000.,"[(17, 21, 'MONEY'), (30, 35, 'DATE'), (41, 52, 'IP-Address'), (63, 99, 'Token keys')]"
The server rebooted at 1st hour with IP 192.168.0.100 and token key aabbccddeeff11223344556677889900.,"[(22, 25, 'ORDINAL'), (36, 49, 'IP-Address'), (54, 90, 'Token keys')]"
"Maria translated the document into French on 2024-02-20, using IP 172.217.16.14 and token key 123abc456def789ghi012jkl345mno678.","[(0, 5, 'PER'), (39, 45, 'LANGUAGE'), (49, 59, 'DATE'), (67, 79, 'IP-Address'), (90, 126, 'Token keys')]"
Node with IP fe80::abcd:1234:5678:9abc generated token key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788776655443322110 at 2024-06-01.,"[(13, 44, 'IP-Address'), (63, 95, 'Token keys'), (99, 109, 'DATE')]"
Company 'Net Solutions' processed a payment of $1500 from IP 198.51.100.23 using token key 11223344556677889900aabbccddeeff on 2024-05-05.,"[(8, 21, 'ORG'), (44, 48, 'MONEY'), (54, 65, 'IP-Address'), (82, 118, 'Token keys'), (122, 132, 'DATE')]"
The IP 10.20.30.40 was assigned to device with token key 99887766554433221100ffeeddccbbaa at 2024-07-01.,"[(4, 14, 'IP-Address'), (44, 80, 'Token keys'), (84, 94, 'DATE')]"
Server 'Alpha' at location New York (LOC) with IP 172.16.254.10 assigned token key 1a2b3c4d5e6f7g8h9i0jklmnopqrst on 2024-08-15.,"[(8, 13, 'MISC'), (26, 34, 'LOC'), (44, 57, 'IP-Address'), (74, 110, 'Token keys'), (114, 124, 'DATE')]"
User John Smith speaks German and logged in on 2023-09-30 from IP 203.0.113.99 with token key abcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefab.,"[(5, 15, 'PER'), (23, 29, 'LANGUAGE'), (43, 53, 'DATE'), (59, 70, 'IP-Address'), (81, 117, 'Token keys')]"
The file transfer of 500MB was done on 2024-01-05 from IP 192.0.2.5 using token key 123456abcdef7890123456abcdef7890.,"[(18, 22, 'QUANTITY'), (32, 42, 'DATE'), (48, 57, 'IP-Address'), (69, 105, 'Token keys')]"
Device with IP 2404:6800:4003:c03::8a2e:370:7335 logged event at 2nd hour using token key 0a1b2c3d4e5f6g7h8i9jklmnopqrstuvw.,"[(14, 44, 'IP-Address'), (64, 67, 'ORDINAL'), (83, 119, 'Token keys')]"
Email sent by Alice Johnson on 2023-11-20 from IP 198.51.100.100 with token key abc123def456ghi789jkl012mno345pq.,"[(14, 28, 'PER'), (32, 42, 'DATE'), (48, 61, 'IP-Address'), (72, 108, 'Token keys')]"
The server at London with IP 10.10.10.11 issued token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890 on 2024-07-07.,"[(14, 20, 'LOC'), (26, 37, 'IP-Address'), (52, 88, 'Token keys'), (92, 102, 'DATE')]"
Backup size of 1024GB completed on 2024-03-15 from IP 192.168.1.10 with token key zyxwvutsrqponmlkjihgfedcba987654.,"[(15, 19, 'QUANTITY'), (30, 40, 'DATE'), (46, 57, 'IP-Address'), (68, 104, 'Token keys')]"
User with ID 54321 accessed the application using IP 172.217.3.110 and token key 1234abcd5678efgh9012ijkl3456mnop at 2024-02-28.,"[(13, 18, 'CARDINAL'), (59, 70, 'IP-Address'), (85, 121, 'Token keys'), (125, 135, 'DATE')]"
The translation was done by Carlos in Portuguese from IP 203.0.113.45 using token key ffffffff00000000ffffffff00000000.,"[(24, 30, 'PER'), (34, 44, 'LANGUAGE'), (50, 61, 'IP-Address'), (72, 108, 'Token keys')]"
"IP 10.1.1.1 detected anomaly at 5th hour, token key 1a2b3c4d5e6f7g8h9i0jklmnopqrstuv active.","[(3, 12, 'IP-Address'), (31, 34, 'ORDINAL'), (42, 78, 'Token keys')]"
Data export of 2500 records finished on 2024-06-05 from IP 192.168.100.100 with token key abcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefab.,"[(15, 19, 'QUANTITY'), (39, 49, 'DATE'), (55, 69, 'IP-Address'), (80, 116, 'Token keys')]"
The novel 'Sunrise' was accessed by user ID 87654 from IP 198.51.100.50 on 2023-11-01 with token key 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef.,"[(10, 17, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (42, 47, 'CARDINAL'), (53, 65, 'IP-Address'), (69, 79, 'DATE'), (95, 131, 'Token keys')]"
Server at IP 2607:f8b0:4005:805::200e rebooted on 2024-05-20 with token key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788776655443322110.,"[(13, 47, 'IP-Address'), (58, 68, 'DATE'), (82, 114, 'Token keys')]"
Payment of $300 was made by Michael on 2024-04-10 from IP 203.0.113.60 with token key 11223344556677889900aabbccddeeff.,"[(11, 15, 'MONEY'), (29, 36, 'PER'), (40, 50, 'DATE'), (56, 67, 'IP-Address'), (78, 114, 'Token keys')]"
User Anna accessed the platform from IP 10.0.0.1 with token key 99887766554433221100ffeeddccbbaa on 2024-07-15.,"[(5, 9, 'PER'), (44, 51, 'IP-Address'), (62, 98, 'Token keys'), (102, 112, 'DATE')]"
The book 'Odyssey' was downloaded by user ID 65789 from IP 192.168.1.5 on 2023-12-12 with token key abc123def456ghi789jkl012mno345pq.,"[(9, 16, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (41, 46, 'CARDINAL'), (52, 63, 'IP-Address'), (67, 77, 'DATE'), (93, 129, 'Token keys')]"
Backup of 2048GB completed on 2024-01-30 from IP 172.16.0.20 using token key ffffffff00000000ffffffff00000000.,"[(10, 14, 'QUANTITY'), (24, 34, 'DATE'), (40, 51, 'IP-Address'), (62, 98, 'Token keys')]"
The server located in Sydney (LOC) with IP 203.0.113.5 generated token key 1a2b3c4d5e6f7g8h9i0jklmnopqrstuv on 2024-08-20.,"[(25, 31, 'LOC'), (41, 52, 'IP-Address'), (69, 105, 'Token keys'), (109, 119, 'DATE')]"
User with ID 43210 logged in from IP 8.8.4.4 on 2024-03-03 using token key 1234abcd5678efgh9012ijkl3456mnop.,"[(13, 18, 'CARDINAL'), (38, 45, 'IP-Address'), (49, 59, 'DATE'), (70, 106, 'Token keys')]"
Translator Elena used the language Italian on 2024-02-10 to process data from IP 192.168.0.200 with token key zyxwvutsrqponmlkjihgfedcba987654.,"[(11, 16, 'PER'), (30, 37, 'LANGUAGE'), (41, 51, 'DATE'), (69, 82, 'IP-Address'), (93, 129, 'Token keys')]"
The device with IP fe80::abcd:1234:5678:9abc was assigned token key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788776655443322110 on 2024-06-10.,"[(17, 48, 'IP-Address'), (69, 101, 'Token keys'), (105, 115, 'DATE')]"
Company 'Alpha Systems' transferred $1200 from IP 198.51.100.40 with token key abcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefab on 2024-05-10.,"[(8, 22, 'ORG'), (33, 37, 'MONEY'), (43, 54, 'IP-Address'), (71, 107, 'Token keys'), (111, 121, 'DATE')]"
IP 10.20.20.20 was allocated to device with token key 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef on 2024-07-10.,"[(3, 13, 'IP-Address'), (44, 80, 'Token keys'), (84, 94, 'DATE')]"
Server 'Beta' in location Berlin (LOC) with IP 172.16.254.20 issued token key 1a2b3c4d5e6f7g8h9i0jklmnopqrst on 2024-08-20.,"[(8, 12, 'MISC'), (26, 32, 'LOC'), (42, 55, 'IP-Address'), (72, 108, 'Token keys'), (112, 122, 'DATE')]"
User Mike speaks English and logged in on 2023-09-15 from IP 203.0.113.80 with token key abcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefab.,"[(5, 9, 'PER'), (16, 23, 'LANGUAGE'), (37, 47, 'DATE'), (53, 64, 'IP-Address'), (75, 111, 'Token keys')]"
File transfer of 750MB completed on 2024-01-10 from IP 192.0.2.10 using token key 123456abcdef7890123456abcdef7890.,"[(18, 22, 'QUANTITY'), (32, 42, 'DATE'), (48, 57, 'IP-Address'), (69, 105, 'Token keys')]"
Device with IP 2404:6800:4003:c03::8a2e:370:7336 logged event on 3rd hour using token key 0a1b2c3d4e5f6g7h8i9jklmnopqrstuvw.,"[(14, 44, 'IP-Address'), (60, 63, 'ORDINAL'), (79, 115, 'Token keys')]"
Email sent by Daniel on 2023-11-25 from IP 198.51.100.110 with token key abc123def456ghi789jkl012mno345pq.,"[(14, 20, 'PER'), (24, 34, 'DATE'), (40, 53, 'IP-Address'), (64, 100, 'Token keys')]"
Server at location Madrid with IP 10.10.10.12 generated token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890 on 2024-07-17.,"[(22, 28, 'LOC'), (34, 45, 'IP-Address'), (62, 98, 'Token keys'), (102, 112, 'DATE')]"
Backup size of 512GB completed on 2024-03-18 from IP 192.168.1.15 with token key zyxwvutsrqponmlkjihgfedcba987654.,"[(15, 18, 'QUANTITY'), (28, 38, 'DATE'), (44, 55, 'IP-Address'), (66, 102, 'Token keys')]"
User with ID 67890 logged in from IP 8.8.8.8 on 2024-03-10 using token key 1234abcd5678efgh9012ijkl3456mnop.,"[(13, 18, 'CARDINAL'), (39, 46, 'IP-Address'), (50, 60, 'DATE'), (71, 107, 'Token keys')]"
Translator Anna used the language Dutch on 2024-02-15 to process data from IP 192.168.0.210 with token key zyxwvutsrqponmlkjihgfedcba987654.,"[(11, 15, 'PER'), (29, 34, 'LANGUAGE'), (38, 48, 'DATE'), (66, 79, 'IP-Address'), (90, 126, 'Token keys')]"
The device with IP fe80::abcd:1234:5678:9abd was assigned token key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788776655443322110 on 2024-06-15.,"[(17, 48, 'IP-Address'), (69, 101, 'Token keys'), (105, 115, 'DATE')]"
Company 'BetaTech' transferred $1800 from IP 198.51.100.45 with token key abcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefab on 2024-05-15.,"[(8, 16, 'ORG'), (31, 35, 'MONEY'), (41, 52, 'IP-Address'), (69, 105, 'Token keys'), (109, 119, 'DATE')]"
IP 10.20.30.30 was allocated to device with token key 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef on 2024-07-20.,"[(3, 13, 'IP-Address'), (44, 80, 'Token keys'), (84, 94, 'DATE')]"
Server 'Gamma' in location Rome with IP 172.16.254.30 issued token key 1a2b3c4d5e6f7g8h9i0jklmnopqrst on 2024-08-25.,"[(8, 13, 'MISC'), (27, 31, 'LOC'), (41, 54, 'IP-Address'), (71, 107, 'Token keys'), (111, 121, 'DATE')]"
User Emma speaks Swedish and logged in on 2023-09-20 from IP 203.0.113.90 with token key abcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefab.,"[(5, 9, 'PER'), (16, 23, 'LANGUAGE'), (37, 47, 'DATE'), (53, 64, 'IP-Address'), (75, 111, 'Token keys')]"
File transfer of 900MB completed on 2024-01-15 from IP 192.0.2.15 using token key 123456abcdef7890123456abcdef7890.,"[(18, 22, 'QUANTITY'), (32, 42, 'DATE'), (48, 57, 'IP-Address'), (69, 105, 'Token keys')]"
Device with IP 2404:6800:4003:c03::8a2e:370:7337 logged event on 4th hour using token key 0a1b2c3d4e5f6g7h8i9jklmnopqrstuvw.,"[(14, 44, 'IP-Address'), (60, 62, 'ORDINAL'), (79, 115, 'Token keys')]"
Email sent by David on 2023-11-30 from IP 198.51.100.120 with token key abc123def456ghi789jkl012mno345pq.,"[(14, 19, 'PER'), (23, 33, 'DATE'), (39, 52, 'IP-Address'), (63, 99, 'Token keys')]"
Server at location Rome (LOC) with IP 10.10.10.13 generated token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890 on 2024-07-22.,"[(22, 26, 'LOC'), (32, 43, 'IP-Address'), (60, 96, 'Token keys'), (100, 110, 'DATE')]"
Backup size of 1024GB completed on 2024-03-20 from IP 192.168.1.20 with token key zyxwvutsrqponmlkjihgfedcba987654.,"[(15, 19, 'QUANTITY'), (29, 39, 'DATE'), (45, 56, 'IP-Address'), (67, 103, 'Token keys')]"
User with ID 98765 logged in from IP 8.8.8.4 on 2024-03-15 using token key 1234abcd5678efgh9012ijkl3456mnop.,"[(13, 18, 'CARDINAL'), (39, 46, 'IP-Address'), (50, 60, 'DATE'), (71, 107, 'Token keys')]"
Translator Laura used the language Finnish on 2024-02-20 to process data from IP 192.168.0.220 with token key zyxwvutsrqponmlkjihgfedcba987654.,"[(11, 16, 'PER'), (30, 37, 'LANGUAGE'), (41, 51, 'DATE'), (69, 82, 'IP-Address'), (93, 129, 'Token keys')]"
The device with IP fe80::abcd:1234:5678:9abe was assigned token key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788776655443322110 on 2024-06-20.,"[(17, 48, 'IP-Address'), (69, 101, 'Token keys'), (105, 115, 'DATE')]"
Company 'GammaTech' transferred $2000 from IP 198.51.100.55 with token key abcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefab on 2024-05-20.,"[(8, 18, 'ORG'), (33, 37, 'MONEY'), (43, 54, 'IP-Address'), (71, 107, 'Token keys'), (111, 121, 'DATE')]"
IP 10.20.40.40 was allocated to device with token key 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef on 2024-07-25.,"[(3, 13, 'IP-Address'), (44, 80, 'Token keys'), (84, 94, 'DATE')]"
Server 'Delta' in location Paris (LOC) with IP 172.16.254.40 issued token key 1a2b3c4d5e6f7g8h9i0jklmnopqrst on 2024-08-30.,"[(8, 13, 'MISC'), (27, 32, 'LOC'), (42, 55, 'IP-Address'), (72, 108, 'Token keys'), (112, 122, 'DATE')]"
User Olivia speaks Norwegian and logged in on 2023-09-25 from IP 203.0.113.100 with token key abcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefab.,"[(5, 11, 'PER'), (19, 27, 'LANGUAGE'), (41, 51, 'DATE'), (57, 68, 'IP-Address'), (79, 115, 'Token keys')]"
File transfer of 850MB completed on 2024-01-20 from IP 192.0.2.20 using token key 123456abcdef7890123456abcdef7890.,"[(18, 22, 'QUANTITY'), (32, 42, 'DATE'), (48, 57, 'IP-Address'), (69, 105, 'Token keys')]"
Device with IP 2404:6800:4003:c03::8a2e:370:7338 logged event on 5th hour using token key 0a1b2c3d4e5f6g7h8i9jklmnopqrstuvw.,"[(14, 44, 'IP-Address'), (60, 62, 'ORDINAL'), (79, 115, 'Token keys')]"
Email sent by Sophia on 2023-12-05 from IP 198.51.100.130 with token key abc123def456ghi789jkl012mno345pq.,"[(14, 20, 'PER'), (24, 34, 'DATE'), (40, 53, 'IP-Address'), (64, 100, 'Token keys')]"
Server at location Berlin with IP 10.10.10.14 generated token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890 on 2024-07-30.,"[(22, 28, 'LOC'), (34, 45, 'IP-Address'), (62, 98, 'Token keys'), (102, 112, 'DATE')]"
Backup size of 2048GB completed on 2024-03-25 from IP 192.168.1.25 with token key zyxwvutsrqponmlkjihgfedcba987654.,"[(15, 19, 'QUANTITY'), (29, 39, 'DATE'), (45, 56, 'IP-Address'), (67, 103, 'Token keys')]"
User with ID 11223 logged in from IP 8.8.8.5 on 2024-03-20 using token key 1234abcd5678efgh9012ijkl3456mnop.,"[(13, 18, 'CARDINAL'), (39, 46, 'IP-Address'), (50, 60, 'DATE'), (71, 107, 'Token keys')]"
Translator Lucas used the language Danish on 2024-02-25 to process data from IP 192.168.0.230 with token key zyxwvutsrqponmlkjihgfedcba987654.,"[(11, 16, 'PER'), (30, 36, 'LANGUAGE'), (40, 50, 'DATE'), (68, 81, 'IP-Address'), (92, 128, 'Token keys')]"
The device with IP fe80::abcd:1234:5678:9abf was assigned token key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788776655443322110 on 2024-06-25.,"[(17, 48, 'IP-Address'), (69, 101, 'Token keys'), (105, 115, 'DATE')]"
Company 'DeltaTech' transferred $2200 from IP 198.51.100.65 with token key abcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefab on 2024-05-25.,"[(8, 18, 'ORG'), (33, 37, 'MONEY'), (43, 54, 'IP-Address'), (71, 107, 'Token keys'), (111, 121, 'DATE')]"
IP 10.20.50.50 was allocated to device with token key 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef on 2024-07-30.,"[(3, 13, 'IP-Address'), (44, 80, 'Token keys'), (84, 94, 'DATE')]"
Server 'Epsilon' in location Vienna with IP 172.16.254.50 issued token key 1a2b3c4d5e6f7g8h9i0jklmnopqrst on 2024-09-01.,"[(8, 15, 'MISC'), (29, 35, 'LOC'), (45, 58, 'IP-Address'), (75, 111, 'Token keys'), (115, 125, 'DATE')]"
User Mia speaks Finnish and logged in on 2023-10-01 from IP 203.0.113.110 with token key abcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefab.,"[(5, 8, 'PER'), (15, 22, 'LANGUAGE'), (36, 46, 'DATE'), (52, 63, 'IP-Address'), (74, 110, 'Token keys')]"
File transfer of 950MB completed on 2024-01-25 from IP 192.0.2.25 using token key 123456abcdef7890123456abcdef7890.,"[(18, 22, 'QUANTITY'), (32, 42, 'DATE'), (48, 57, 'IP-Address'), (69, 105, 'Token keys')]"
Device with IP 2404:6800:4003:c03::8a2e:370:7339 logged event on 6th hour using token key 0a1b2c3d4e5f6g7h8i9jklmnopqrstuvw.,"[(14, 44, 'IP-Address'), (60, 62, 'ORDINAL'), (79, 115, 'Token keys')]"
Email sent by Liam on 2023-12-10 from IP 198.51.100.140 with token key abc123def456ghi789jkl012mno345pq.,"[(14, 18, 'PER'), (22, 32, 'DATE'), (38, 51, 'IP-Address'), (62, 98, 'Token keys')]"
Server at location Madrid with IP 10.10.10.15 generated token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890 on 2024-08-01.,"[(22, 28, 'LOC'), (34, 45, 'IP-Address'), (62, 98, 'Token keys'), (102, 112, 'DATE')]"
Backup size of 3072GB completed on 2024-03-30 from IP 192.168.1.30 with token key zyxwvutsrqponmlkjihgfedcba987654.,"[(15, 19, 'QUANTITY'), (29, 39, 'DATE'), (45, 56, 'IP-Address'), (67, 103, 'Token keys')]"
User with ID 13579 logged in from IP 8.8.8.6 on 2024-03-25 using token key 1234abcd5678efgh9012ijkl3456mnop.,"[(13, 18, 'CARDINAL'), (39, 46, 'IP-Address'), (50, 60, 'DATE'), (71, 107, 'Token keys')]"
Translator Eva used the language Norwegian on 2024-03-01 to process data from IP 192.168.0.240 with token key zyxwvutsrqponmlkjihgfedcba987654.,"[(11, 14, 'PER'), (28, 36, 'LANGUAGE'), (40, 50, 'DATE'), (68, 81, 'IP-Address'), (92, 128, 'Token keys')]"
The device with IP fe80::abcd:1234:5678:9ac0 was assigned token key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788776655443322110 on 2024-06-30.,"[(17, 48, 'IP-Address'), (69, 101, 'Token keys'), (105, 115, 'DATE')]"
Company 'EpsilonTech' transferred $2500 from IP 198.51.100.75 with token key abcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefab on 2024-05-30.,"[(8, 20, 'ORG'), (35, 39, 'MONEY'), (45, 56, 'IP-Address'), (73, 109, 'Token keys'), (113, 123, 'DATE')]"
IP 10.20.60.60 was allocated to device with token key 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef on 2024-08-05.,"[(3, 13, 'IP-Address'), (44, 80, 'Token keys'), (84, 94, 'DATE')]"
Server 'Zeta' in location Amsterdam with IP 172.16.254.60 issued token key 1a2b3c4d5e6f7g8h9i0jklmnopqrst on 2024-09-05.,"[(8, 12, 'MISC'), (26, 35, 'LOC'), (45, 58, 'IP-Address'), (75, 111, 'Token keys'), (115, 125, 'DATE')]"
User Noah speaks Danish and logged in on 2023-10-05 from IP 203.0.113.120 with token key abcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefab.,"[(5, 9, 'PER'), (16, 22, 'LANGUAGE'), (36, 46, 'DATE'), (52, 63, 'IP-Address'), (74, 110, 'Token keys')]"
File transfer of 1000MB completed on 2024-01-30 from IP 192.0.2.30 using token key 123456abcdef7890123456abcdef7890.,"[(18, 22, 'QUANTITY'), (32, 42, 'DATE'), (48, 57, 'IP-Address'), (69, 105, 'Token keys')]"
Device with IP 2404:6800:4003:c03::8a2e:370:7340 logged event on 7th hour using token key 0a1b2c3d4e5f6g7h8i9jklmnopqrstuvw.,"[(14, 44, 'IP-Address'), (60, 62, 'ORDINAL'), (79, 115, 'Token keys')]"
Email sent by Ethan on 2023-12-15 from IP 198.51.100.150 with token key abc123def456ghi789jkl012mno345pq.,"[(14, 19, 'PER'), (23, 33, 'DATE'), (39, 52, 'IP-Address'), (63, 99, 'Token keys')]"
Server at location Lisbon with IP 10.10.10.16 generated token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890 on 2024-08-05.,"[(22, 28, 'LOC'), (34, 45, 'IP-Address'), (62, 98, 'Token keys'), (102, 112, 'DATE')]"
Backup size of 4096GB completed on 2024-04-01 from IP 192.168.1.35 with token key zyxwvutsrqponmlkjihgfedcba987654.,"[(15, 19, 'QUANTITY'), (29, 39, 'DATE'), (45, 56, 'IP-Address'), (67, 103, 'Token keys')]"
User with ID 24680 logged in from IP 8.8.8.7 on 2024-03-30 using token key 1234abcd5678efgh9012ijkl3456mnop.,"[(13, 18, 'CARDINAL'), (39, 46, 'IP-Address'), (50, 60, 'DATE'), (71, 107, 'Token keys')]"
Translator Noah used the language Swedish on 2024-03-05 to process data from IP 192.168.0.250 with token key zyxwvutsrqponmlkjihgfedcba987654.,"[(11, 15, 'PER'), (29, 36, 'LANGUAGE'), (40, 50, 'DATE'), (68, 81, 'IP-Address'), (92, 128, 'Token keys')]"
The device with IP fe80::abcd:1234:5678:9ac1 was assigned token key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788776655443322110 on 2024-07-01.,"[(17, 48, 'IP-Address'), (69, 101, 'Token keys'), (105, 115, 'DATE')]"
Company 'ZetaTech' transferred $2700 from IP 198.51.100.85 with token key abcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefab on 2024-06-01.,"[(8, 18, 'ORG'), (33, 37, 'MONEY'), (43, 54, 'IP-Address'), (71, 107, 'Token keys'), (111, 121, 'DATE')]"
IP 10.20.70.70 was allocated to device with token key 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef on 2024-08-10.,"[(3, 13, 'IP-Address'), (44, 80, 'Token keys'), (84, 94, 'DATE')]"
Server 'Theta' in location Brussels with IP 172.16.254.70 issued token key 1a2b3c4d5e6f7g8h9i0jklmnopqrst on 2024-09-10.,"[(8, 13, 'MISC'), (27, 34, 'LOC'), (44, 57, 'IP-Address'), (74, 110, 'Token keys'), (114, 124, 'DATE')]"
User Ava speaks Dutch and logged in on 2023-10-10 from IP 203.0.113.130 with token key abcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefab.,"[(5, 8, 'PER'), (15, 20, 'LANGUAGE'), (34, 44, 'DATE'), (50, 61, 'IP-Address'), (72, 108, 'Token keys')]"
File transfer of 1100MB completed on 2024-02-01 from IP 192.0.2.35 using token key 123456abcdef7890123456abcdef7890.,"[(18, 22, 'QUANTITY'), (32, 42, 'DATE'), (48, 57, 'IP-Address'), (69, 105, 'Token keys')]"
Device with IP 2404:6800:4003:c03::8a2e:370:7341 logged event on 8th hour using token key 0a1b2c3d4e5f6g7h8i9jklmnopqrstuvw.,"[(14, 44, 'IP-Address'), (60, 62, 'ORDINAL'), (79, 115, 'Token keys')]"
Email sent by Emma on 2023-12-20 from IP 198.51.100.160 with token key abc123def456ghi789jkl012mno345pq.,"[(14, 18, 'PER'), (22, 32, 'DATE'), (38, 51, 'IP-Address'), (62, 98, 'Token keys')]"
Server at location Oslo with IP 10.10.10.17 generated token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890 on 2024-08-10.,"[(22, 26, 'LOC'), (32, 43, 'IP-Address'), (60, 96, 'Token keys'), (100, 110, 'DATE')]"
Backup size of 5120GB completed on 2024-04-05 from IP 192.168.1.40 with token key zyxwvutsrqponmlkjihgfedcba987654.,"[(15, 19, 'QUANTITY'), (29, 39, 'DATE'), (45, 56, 'IP-Address'), (67, 103, 'Token keys')]"
User with ID 35791 logged in from IP 8.8.8.8 on 2024-04-01 using token key 1234abcd5678efgh9012ijkl3456mnop.,"[(13, 18, 'CARDINAL'), (39, 46, 'IP-Address'), (50, 60, 'DATE'), (71, 107, 'Token keys')]"
Translator Liam used the language Swedish on 2024-03-10 to process data from IP 192.168.0.245 with token key zyxwvutsrqponmlkjihgfedcba987654.,"[(11, 15, 'PER'), (29, 36, 'LANGUAGE'), (40, 50, 'DATE'), (68, 81, 'IP-Address'), (92, 128, 'Token keys')]"
The device with IP fe80::abcd:1234:5678:9ac2 was assigned token key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788776655443322110 on 2024-07-05.,"[(17, 48, 'IP-Address'), (69, 101, 'Token keys'), (105, 115, 'DATE')]"
Company 'ThetaTech' transferred $2800 from IP 198.51.100.95 with token key abcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefab on 2024-06-05.,"[(8, 18, 'ORG'), (33, 37, 'MONEY'), (43, 54, 'IP-Address'), (71, 107, 'Token keys'), (111, 121, 'DATE')]"
IP 10.20.80.80 was allocated to device with token key 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef on 2024-08-15.,"[(3, 13, 'IP-Address'), (44, 80, 'Token keys'), (84, 94, 'DATE')]"
Server 'Iota' in location Helsinki with IP 172.16.254.80 issued token key 1a2b3c4d5e6f7g8h9i0jklmnopqrst on 2024-09-15.,"[(8, 13, 'MISC'), (27, 34, 'LOC'), (44, 57, 'IP-Address'), (74, 110, 'Token keys'), (114, 124, 'DATE')]"
User Sophia speaks Spanish and logged in on 2023-10-15 from IP 203.0.113.140 with token key abcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefab.,"[(5, 11, 'PER'), (19, 26, 'LANGUAGE'), (40, 50, 'DATE'), (56, 67, 'IP-Address'), (78, 114, 'Token keys')]"
File transfer of 1150MB completed on 2024-02-05 from IP 192.0.2.40 using token key 123456abcdef7890123456abcdef7890.,"[(18, 22, 'QUANTITY'), (32, 42, 'DATE'), (48, 57, 'IP-Address'), (69, 105, 'Token keys')]"
Device with IP 2404:6800:4003:c03::8a2e:370:7342 logged event on 9th hour using token key 0a1b2c3d4e5f6g7h8i9jklmnopqrstuvw.,"[(14, 44, 'IP-Address'), (60, 62, 'ORDINAL'), (79, 115, 'Token keys')]"
Email sent by Ava on 2023-12-25 from IP 198.51.100.170 with token key abc123def456ghi789jkl012mno345pq.,"[(14, 17, 'PER'), (21, 31, 'DATE'), (37, 50, 'IP-Address'), (61, 97, 'Token keys')]"
Server at location Zurich with IP 10.10.10.18 generated token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890 on 2024-08-15.,"[(22, 28, 'LOC'), (34, 45, 'IP-Address'), (62, 98, 'Token keys'), (102, 112, 'DATE')]"
Backup size of 6144GB completed on 2024-04-10 from IP 192.168.1.45 with token key zyxwvutsrqponmlkjihgfedcba987654.,"[(15, 19, 'QUANTITY'), (29, 39, 'DATE'), (45, 56, 'IP-Address'), (67, 103, 'Token keys')]"
User with ID 46802 logged in from IP 8.8.8.9 on 2024-04-05 using token key 1234abcd5678efgh9012ijkl3456mnop.,"[(13, 18, 'CARDINAL'), (39, 46, 'IP-Address'), (50, 60, 'DATE'), (71, 107, 'Token keys')]"
Translator Mia used the language German on 2024-03-15 to process data from IP 192.168.0.255 with token key zyxwvutsrqponmlkjihgfedcba987654.,"[(11, 14, 'PER'), (28, 34, 'LANGUAGE'), (38, 48, 'DATE'), (66, 79, 'IP-Address'), (90, 126, 'Token keys')]"
The device with IP fe80::abcd:1234:5678:9ac3 was assigned token key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788776655443322110 on 2024-07-10.,"[(17, 48, 'IP-Address'), (69, 101, 'Token keys'), (105, 115, 'DATE')]"
Company 'IotaTech' transferred $3000 from IP 198.51.100.105 with token key abcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefab on 2024-06-10.,"[(8, 18, 'ORG'), (33, 37, 'MONEY'), (43, 54, 'IP-Address'), (71, 107, 'Token keys'), (111, 121, 'DATE')]"
IP 10.20.90.90 was allocated to device with token key 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef on 2024-08-20.,"[(3, 13, 'IP-Address'), (44, 80, 'Token keys'), (84, 94, 'DATE')]"
Server 'Kappa' in location Helsinki with IP 172.16.254.90 issued token key 1a2b3c4d5e6f7g8h9i0jklmnopqrst on 2024-09-20.,"[(8, 13, 'MISC'), (27, 34, 'LOC'), (44, 57, 'IP-Address'), (74, 110, 'Token keys'), (114, 124, 'DATE')]"
User Isabella speaks Norwegian and logged in on 2023-10-20 from IP 203.0.113.150 with token key abcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefab.,"[(5, 13, 'PER'), (21, 29, 'LANGUAGE'), (43, 53, 'DATE'), (59, 70, 'IP-Address'), (81, 117, 'Token keys')]"
File transfer of 1200MB completed on 2024-02-10 from IP 192.0.2.45 using token key 123456abcdef7890123456abcdef7890.,"[(18, 22, 'QUANTITY'), (32, 42, 'DATE'), (48, 57, 'IP-Address'), (69, 105, 'Token keys')]"
Device with IP 2404:6800:4003:c03::8a2e:370:7343 logged event on 10th hour using token key 0a1b2c3d4e5f6g7h8i9jklmnopqrstuvw.,"[(14, 44, 'IP-Address'), (60, 63, 'ORDINAL'), (79, 115, 'Token keys')]"
Email sent by Lucas on 2023-12-30 from IP 198.51.100.180 with token key abc123def456ghi789jkl012mno345pq.,"[(14, 19, 'PER'), (23, 33, 'DATE'), (39, 52, 'IP-Address'), (63, 99, 'Token keys')]"
Server at location Dublin with IP 10.10.10.19 generated token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890 on 2024-08-20.,"[(22, 28, 'LOC'), (34, 45, 'IP-Address'), (62, 98, 'Token keys'), (102, 112, 'DATE')]"
The API request with token 4f9b8d7e3c2a1f0b9e8d7c6a5b4f3e2d was received from IP 192.168.1.101 on 2024-05-15 at the New York office of OpenTech.,"[(26, 58, 'Token keys'), (75, 86, 'IP-Address'), (90, 100, 'DATE'), (108, 116, 'LOC'), (124, 131, 'ORG')]"
User authentication succeeded using token 9a8b7c6d5e4f3a2b1c0d9e8f7b6a5c4d from IP 2001:0db8:85a3:0000:0000:8a2e:0370:7334 on 15 June 2024 at Berlin HQ.,"[(38, 74, 'Token keys'), (80, 117, 'IP-Address'), (121, 132, 'DATE'), (136, 142, 'LOC'), (143, 146, 'ORG')]"
"The license key d4e5f6a7b8c9d0e1f2a3b4c5d6e7f8a9 was registered from IP 10.0.0.45 on March 3rd, 2024 in San Francisco by developer Alice Johnson.","[(16, 52, 'Token keys'), (69, 77, 'IP-Address'), (81, 96, 'DATE'), (100, 113, 'LOC'), (117, 130, 'PER')]"
Error code 503 triggered for token 7f6e5d4c3b2a1908f7e6d5c4b3a2e1d0 on IP 172.16.254.1 at London branch of CyberSys on 2024-01-22.,"[(19, 55, 'Token keys'), (63, 75, 'IP-Address'), (79, 85, 'LOC'), (95, 102, 'ORG'), (106, 116, 'DATE')]"
Session ID b1c2d3e4f5a6b7c8d9e0f1a2b3c4d5e6 was logged from IPv6 address fe80::f2de:f1ff:fe3f:307e on 07/12/2024 at Tokyo main office.,"[(11, 47, 'Token keys'), (67, 85, 'IP-Address'), (89, 99, 'DATE'), (103, 108, 'LOC')]"
"Payment of $1250 was processed with token a9b8c7d6e5f4a3b2c1d0e9f8a7b6c5d4 from IP 203.0.113.77 on April 10, 2024 by Finance Dept.","[(22, 58, 'Token keys'), (65, 77, 'IP-Address'), (81, 94, 'DATE'), (98, 110, 'ORG'), (11, 16, 'MONEY')]"
Token e3d4c5b6a7f8e9d0c1b2a3f4d5e6c7b8 authorized access from IPv4 198.51.100.23 on 2024-04-01 at Paris branch of GlobalSoft.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (70, 82, 'IP-Address'), (86, 96, 'DATE'), (100, 105, 'LOC'), (115, 124, 'ORG')]"
New deployment initiated with token 1a2b3c4d5e6f7g8h9i0j1k2l3m4n5o6p from IP 192.0.2.44 on 2024-02-28 in Madrid by DevOps team.,"[(29, 65, 'Token keys'), (72, 83, 'IP-Address'), (87, 97, 'DATE'), (101, 107, 'LOC'), (111, 119, 'ORG')]"
License token 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788796a5b4c3d2e1f0 detected from IPv6 2607:f8b0:4005:805::200e at Googleplex HQ on 2024-03-10.,"[(14, 50, 'Token keys'), (68, 93, 'IP-Address'), (97, 108, 'ORG'), (112, 120, 'ORG'), (124, 134, 'DATE')]"
The software key 9d8c7b6a5e4f3d2c1b0a9e8f7d6c5b4a was used from IP 8.8.8.8 at Seattle office on 12/24/2024 by engineer Bob Smith.,"[(17, 53, 'Token keys'), (60, 67, 'IP-Address'), (71, 77, 'LOC'), (81, 91, 'DATE'), (95, 105, 'PER')]"
Token 4a3b2c1d0e9f8a7b6c5d4e3f2a1b0c9d8 failed login from IP 172.31.255.255 on 2024-06-01 at Mumbai data center.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (59, 74, 'IP-Address'), (78, 88, 'DATE'), (92, 98, 'LOC')]"
Access granted to token f0e1d2c3b4a5968778695a4b3c2d1e0f from IPv4 127.0.0.1 on 01-05-2024 in Toronto by manager Maria Lopez.,"[(18, 54, 'Token keys'), (62, 72, 'IP-Address'), (76, 86, 'DATE'), (90, 97, 'LOC'), (101, 113, 'PER')]"
The encryption token c9b8a7d6e5f40312ab45cd67e89f0123 was logged from IP 203.0.113.195 on 2024-07-15 at Berlin office of DataCorp.,"[(21, 57, 'Token keys'), (64, 76, 'IP-Address'), (80, 90, 'DATE'), (94, 100, 'LOC'), (109, 116, 'ORG')]"
"Token 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef used from IPv6 2001:0db8:85a3:0000:0000:8a2e:0370:7334 on March 15, 2024 at Sydney headquarters.","[(6, 38, 'Token keys'), (46, 83, 'IP-Address'), (87, 100, 'DATE'), (104, 111, 'LOC')]"
User session token fa12bc34de56f7890a1b2c3d4e5f6789 was initiated from IP 10.10.10.10 on 2024-04-20 at London branch of TechSolutions.,"[(13, 49, 'Token keys'), (66, 76, 'IP-Address'), (80, 90, 'DATE'), (94, 100, 'LOC'), (110, 123, 'ORG')]"
System update verified with token 0a1b2c3d4e5f6a7b8c9d0e1f2a3b4c5d from IPv4 192.168.100.100 on 2024-08-05 at Chicago data center.,"[(23, 59, 'Token keys'), (67, 82, 'IP-Address'), (86, 96, 'DATE'), (100, 107, 'LOC')]"
Authentication token f1e2d3c4b5a69788796a5b4c3d2e1f0a was used from IP 198.51.100.1 on 2024-09-10 at New Delhi branch of SecureNet.,"[(23, 59, 'Token keys'), (66, 78, 'IP-Address'), (82, 92, 'DATE'), (96, 104, 'LOC'), (114, 121, 'ORG')]"
The key 5f4e3d2c1b0a9f8e7d6c5b4a3e2f1d0c was detected from IPv6 address 2606:4700:4700::1111 on 2024-10-01 at Paris office.,"[(12, 48, 'Token keys'), (68, 89, 'IP-Address'), (93, 103, 'DATE'), (107, 112, 'LOC')]"
Token 9e8d7c6b5a4f3e2d1c0b9a8f7d6c5b4a was used for transaction of $3000 from IP 172.217.11.14 on 2024-11-20 at Google HQ.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (67, 72, 'MONEY'), (78, 91, 'IP-Address'), (95, 105, 'DATE'), (109, 115, 'ORG')]"
Access token aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 was logged from IPv4 203.0.113.22 on 2024-12-31 at Tokyo branch of NipponTech.,"[(13, 49, 'Token keys'), (59, 71, 'IP-Address'), (75, 85, 'DATE'), (89, 94, 'LOC'), (104, 115, 'ORG')]"
The token 11223344556677889900aabbccddeeff was activated from IP 192.0.2.123 on 01 January 2024 at Amsterdam data center.,"[(10, 46, 'Token keys'), (56, 67, 'IP-Address'), (71, 85, 'DATE'), (89, 105, 'LOC')]"
VPN connection established using token ffeeddccbbaa99887766554433221100 from IP 172.20.10.5 on 2024-03-05 at Toronto office.,"[(34, 70, 'Token keys'), (77, 88, 'IP-Address'), (92, 102, 'DATE'), (106, 112, 'LOC')]"
Token bbaa99887766554433221100ffeeddcc failed authentication from IPv6 2001:4860:4860::8888 on 2024-05-25 at Seattle branch.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (66, 92, 'IP-Address'), (96, 106, 'DATE'), (110, 117, 'LOC')]"
The session key d4c3b2a1908f7e6d5c4b3a2e1f0d9c8b was revoked after access from IP 10.1.1.1 on 15 March 2024 at Berlin HQ.,"[(16, 52, 'Token keys'), (70, 78, 'IP-Address'), (82, 95, 'DATE'), (99, 105, 'LOC'), (106, 109, 'ORG')]"
Token 99887766554433221100ffeeddccbbaa was generated for user John Doe from IP 192.168.0.200 on 2024-06-15 at London office.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (62, 70, 'PER'), (76, 89, 'IP-Address'), (93, 103, 'DATE'), (107, 113, 'LOC')]"
The API key 123e4567e89b12d3a456426655440000 used from IPv4 8.8.4.4 on 2024-07-30 in New York by admin Emily Clark.,"[(12, 48, 'Token keys'), (56, 63, 'IP-Address'), (67, 77, 'DATE'), (81, 89, 'LOC'), (93, 105, 'PER')]"
Token a1b2c3d4e5f60718293a4b5c6d7e8f90 was used from IP 198.18.0.1 at the Paris office on 2024-09-12 by engineer Liam Chen.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (51, 62, 'IP-Address'), (70, 75, 'LOC'), (79, 89, 'DATE'), (93, 103, 'PER')]"
The software license token 0a9b8c7d6e5f4a3b2c1d0e9f8a7b6c5d was activated from IPv6 2400:cb00:2048:1::c629:d7a2 on 2024-10-05 at Vancouver data center.,"[(24, 60, 'Token keys'), (78, 106, 'IP-Address'), (110, 120, 'DATE'), (124, 132, 'LOC')]"
User token 56789abcde12345f67890abcedf12345 was validated from IP 172.217.5.110 on 2024-08-21 at San Francisco branch.,"[(11, 47, 'Token keys'), (56, 68, 'IP-Address'), (72, 82, 'DATE'), (86, 99, 'LOC')]"
Token 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788796a5b4c3d2e1f0a was logged from IPv4 198.51.100.42 on 2024-11-11 at Amsterdam headquarters.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (60, 75, 'IP-Address'), (79, 89, 'DATE'), (93, 104, 'LOC')]"
Access token fedcba98765432100123456789abcdef was used from IP 10.10.10.254 at London branch on 2024-12-01 by technician Sarah Lee.,"[(13, 49, 'Token keys'), (58, 69, 'IP-Address'), (73, 79, 'LOC'), (83, 93, 'DATE'), (97, 107, 'PER')]"
Token 123abc456def7890abc123def4567890 was revoked after failed login attempt from IP 192.168.100.100 on 2024-01-15 at Tokyo office.,"[(6, 38, 'Token keys'), (76, 89, 'IP-Address'), (93, 103, 'DATE'), (107, 113, 'LOC')]"
The authentication token 4b3a2c1d0e9f8a7b6c5d4e3f2a1b0c9d was used from IPv6 2001:db8::ff00:42:8329 on 2024-02-20 at Berlin branch.,"[(23, 59, 'Token keys'), (77, 95, 'IP-Address'), (99, 109, 'DATE'), (113, 119, 'LOC')]"
"License key aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 was registered from IP 172.16.0.2 on March 1, 2024 at New York office.","[(12, 48, 'Token keys'), (58, 69, 'IP-Address'), (73, 85, 'DATE'), (89, 97, 'LOC')]"
Token 99887766554433221100ffeeddccbbaa authorized access from IPv4 203.0.113.55 on 2024-03-18 at San Francisco HQ.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (70, 82, 'IP-Address'), (86, 96, 'DATE'), (100, 113, 'LOC'), (114, 116, 'ORG')]"
User session token 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788796a5b4c3d2e1f0a was initiated from IP 192.0.2.33 on 2024-04-22 in Chicago by admin David Kim.,"[(13, 49, 'Token keys'), (58, 69, 'IP-Address'), (73, 83, 'DATE'), (87, 94, 'LOC'), (98, 107, 'PER')]"
Token b1c2d3e4f5a6b7c8d9e0f1a2b3c4d5e6 failed to authenticate from IPv6 fe80::1ff:fe23:4567:890a on 2024-05-05 at London office.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (69, 98, 'IP-Address'), (102, 112, 'DATE'), (116, 122, 'LOC')]"
The encryption token 9a8b7c6d5e4f3a2b1c0d9e8f7b6a5c4d was used from IP 10.10.1.1 on 2024-06-10 at Paris headquarters.,"[(19, 55, 'Token keys'), (62, 71, 'IP-Address'), (75, 85, 'DATE'), (89, 98, 'LOC')]"
Token f0e1d2c3b4a5968778695a4b3c2d1e0f authorized access from IP 198.51.100.100 on 2024-07-25 at Tokyo branch.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (68, 83, 'IP-Address'), (87, 97, 'DATE'), (101, 107, 'LOC')]"
User token 5f4e3d2c1b0a9f8e7d6c5b4a3e2f1d0c was created from IPv4 203.0.113.10 on 2024-08-30 at New York office by engineer Anna Wright.,"[(11, 47, 'Token keys'), (56, 68, 'IP-Address'), (72, 82, 'DATE'), (86, 94, 'LOC'), (98, 110, 'PER')]"
The key 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef was detected from IP 192.168.200.200 on 2024-09-15 at London data center.,"[(12, 48, 'Token keys'), (58, 73, 'IP-Address'), (77, 87, 'DATE'), (91, 97, 'LOC')]"
Token 9d8c7b6a5e4f3d2c1b0a9e8f7d6c5b4a failed login from IPv6 2607:f8b0:4005:805::200e on 01-10-2024 at Seattle office.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (60, 85, 'IP-Address'), (89, 99, 'DATE'), (103, 109, 'LOC')]"
Authentication token aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 used from IP 172.31.0.1 on 2024-11-20 at Berlin branch.,"[(18, 54, 'Token keys'), (63, 74, 'IP-Address'), (78, 88, 'DATE'), (92, 98, 'LOC')]"
Session token 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788796a5b4c3d2e1f0a was logged from IPv4 198.51.100.25 on 2024-12-05 at San Francisco office.,"[(14, 50, 'Token keys'), (68, 83, 'IP-Address'), (87, 97, 'DATE'), (101, 116, 'LOC')]"
Token 123abc456def7890abc123def4567890 was authorized from IP 10.0.0.25 on 2024-01-10 at Tokyo HQ by admin Michael Scott.,"[(6, 38, 'Token keys'), (49, 59, 'IP-Address'), (63, 73, 'DATE'), (77, 82, 'LOC'), (86, 101, 'PER')]"
The license key b1c2d3e4f5a6b7c8d9e0f1a2b3c4d5e6 was used from IPv6 fe80::f2de:f1ff:fe3f:307e on 2024-02-15 at Amsterdam branch.,"[(16, 52, 'Token keys'), (70, 88, 'IP-Address'), (92, 102, 'DATE'), (106, 114, 'LOC')]"
Token a9b8c7d6e5f40312ab45cd67e89f0123 was logged from IP 192.168.1.50 on 2024-03-22 at London office by technician Jane Doe.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (54, 67, 'IP-Address'), (71, 81, 'DATE'), (85, 91, 'LOC'), (95, 103, 'PER')]"
User token 99887766554433221100ffeeddccbbaa was generated from IPv4 203.0.113.66 on 2024-04-30 in New York by developer Tom Hanks.,"[(11, 47, 'Token keys'), (56, 68, 'IP-Address'), (72, 82, 'DATE'), (86, 94, 'LOC'), (98, 108, 'PER')]"
Token 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788796a5b4c3d2e1f0a failed authentication from IP 172.16.0.5 on 2024-05-18 at Paris HQ.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (70, 79, 'IP-Address'), (83, 93, 'DATE'), (97, 103, 'LOC'), (104, 106, 'ORG')]"
The encryption token ffeeddccbbaa99887766554433221100 was used from IPv6 2001:4860:4860::8888 on 2024-06-25 at Seattle branch.,"[(19, 55, 'Token keys'), (73, 99, 'IP-Address'), (103, 113, 'DATE'), (117, 124, 'LOC')]"
Token aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 was validated from IP 192.168.100.101 on 2024-07-14 at Tokyo data center.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (51, 66, 'IP-Address'), (70, 80, 'DATE'), (84, 99, 'LOC')]"
User session token 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef was created from IPv4 198.51.100.100 on 2024-08-28 in Berlin by engineer Sarah Connor.,"[(13, 49, 'Token keys'), (58, 73, 'IP-Address'), (77, 87, 'DATE'), (91, 97, 'LOC'), (101, 115, 'PER')]"
Token 9d8c7b6a5e4f3d2c1b0a9e8f7d6c5b4a was used for access from IP 10.10.10.10 on 2024-09-05 at London office.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (60, 70, 'IP-Address'), (74, 84, 'DATE'), (88, 94, 'LOC')]"
The token 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788796a5b4c3d2e1f0a was revoked after suspicious activity from IPv6 2607:f8b0:4005:805::200e on 2024-10-15 at New York branch.,"[(10, 46, 'Token keys'), (90, 108, 'IP-Address'), (112, 122, 'DATE'), (126, 134, 'LOC')]"
Access granted with token aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 from IP 203.0.113.1 on 2024-11-30 at San Francisco HQ by admin John Doe.,"[(21, 57, 'Token keys'), (66, 77, 'IP-Address'), (81, 91, 'DATE'), (95, 108, 'LOC'), (112, 120, 'PER')]"
Authentication token 123e4567e89b12d3a456426655440000 was used from IPv4 8.8.8.8 on 2024-12-12 at Tokyo data center.,"[(23, 59, 'Token keys'), (77, 84, 'IP-Address'), (88, 98, 'DATE'), (102, 117, 'LOC')]"
Token 56789abcde12345f67890abcedf12345 was issued from IP 172.20.10.5 on 2024-01-25 at Berlin office by technician Alice Smith.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (51, 62, 'IP-Address'), (66, 76, 'DATE'), (80, 86, 'LOC'), (90, 102, 'PER')]"
The license key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788796a5b4c3d2e1f0a was activated from IPv6 fe80::f2de:f1ff:fe3f:307e on 2024-02-28 at London headquarters.,"[(16, 52, 'Token keys'), (70, 88, 'IP-Address'), (92, 102, 'DATE'), (106, 116, 'LOC')]"
Token 9a8b7c6d5e4f3a2b1c0d9e8f7b6a5c4d was used from IP 192.168.1.100 on 2024-03-30 at Amsterdam office.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (51, 66, 'IP-Address'), (70, 80, 'DATE'), (84, 100, 'LOC')]"
User token ffeeddccbbaa99887766554433221100 was generated from IPv4 203.0.113.55 on 2024-04-15 in Paris by developer Michael Brown.,"[(11, 47, 'Token keys'), (56, 68, 'IP-Address'), (72, 82, 'DATE'), (86, 91, 'LOC'), (95, 109, 'PER')]"
Token aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 failed login from IP 10.0.0.5 on 2024-05-20 at San Francisco HQ.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (64, 73, 'IP-Address'), (77, 87, 'DATE'), (91, 104, 'LOC')]"
The session key 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef was revoked after unauthorized access from IPv6 2001:db8::ff00:42:8329 on 2024-06-30 at New York branch.,"[(16, 52, 'Token keys'), (105, 123, 'IP-Address'), (127, 137, 'DATE'), (141, 149, 'LOC')]"
Token 9d8c7b6a5e4f3d2c1b0a9e8f7d6c5b4a was authorized from IP 192.168.100.100 on 2024-07-25 at Berlin office by admin Lisa White.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (51, 66, 'IP-Address'), (70, 80, 'DATE'), (84, 90, 'LOC'), (94, 105, 'PER')]"
Access token 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788796a5b4c3d2e1f0a was used from IPv4 198.51.100.42 on 2024-08-15 at Tokyo data center.,"[(13, 49, 'Token keys'), (67, 82, 'IP-Address'), (86, 96, 'DATE'), (100, 115, 'LOC')]"
User token aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 was created from IP 10.10.10.10 on 2024-09-10 in London by engineer Mark Davis.,"[(11, 47, 'Token keys'), (56, 67, 'IP-Address'), (71, 81, 'DATE'), (85, 91, 'LOC'), (95, 106, 'PER')]"
Token 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef was logged from IPv6 fe80::1ff:fe23:4567:890a on 2024-10-05 at San Francisco branch.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (60, 79, 'IP-Address'), (83, 93, 'DATE'), (97, 113, 'LOC')]"
The encryption token 9d8c7b6a5e4f3d2c1b0a9e8f7d6c5b4a was used from IP 172.16.0.10 on 2024-11-20 at Berlin headquarters.,"[(19, 55, 'Token keys'), (64, 75, 'IP-Address'), (79, 89, 'DATE'), (93, 103, 'LOC')]"
Token f0e1d2c3b4a5968778695a4b3c2d1e0f authorized access from IPv4 203.0.113.1 on 2024-12-31 at Tokyo office.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (68, 79, 'IP-Address'), (83, 93, 'DATE'), (97, 103, 'LOC')]"
User session token aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 was initiated from IP 192.168.1.1 on 2024-01-05 in Paris by developer Emma Wilson.,"[(13, 49, 'Token keys'), (58, 69, 'IP-Address'), (73, 83, 'DATE'), (87, 92, 'LOC'), (96, 108, 'PER')]"
Token 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef failed login from IPv6 2607:f8b0:4005:805::200e on 2024-02-18 at London branch.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (60, 87, 'IP-Address'), (91, 101, 'DATE'), (105, 111, 'LOC')]"
The license key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788796a5b4c3d2e1f0a was activated from IP 10.10.10.10 on 2024-03-25 at New York data center.,"[(16, 52, 'Token keys'), (62, 73, 'IP-Address'), (77, 87, 'DATE'), (91, 107, 'LOC')]"
Token 9a8b7c6d5e4f3a2b1c0d9e8f7b6a5c4d was used for authentication from IPv4 198.51.100.100 on 2024-04-30 at San Francisco office.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (72, 87, 'IP-Address'), (91, 101, 'DATE'), (105, 120, 'LOC')]"
Access token ffeeddccbbaa99887766554433221100 was generated from IP 172.16.0.1 on 2024-05-15 at Berlin HQ by technician John Smith.,"[(13, 49, 'Token keys'), (58, 69, 'IP-Address'), (73, 83, 'DATE'), (87, 93, 'LOC'), (97, 107, 'PER')]"
Token aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 was revoked after suspicious activity from IPv6 fe80::f2de:f1ff:fe3f:307e on 2024-06-20 at Tokyo branch.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (87, 105, 'IP-Address'), (109, 119, 'DATE'), (123, 129, 'LOC')]"
User token 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef was created from IP 203.0.113.1 on 2024-07-30 in London by engineer Anna Lee.,"[(11, 47, 'Token keys'), (56, 67, 'IP-Address'), (71, 81, 'DATE'), (85, 91, 'LOC'), (95, 103, 'PER')]"
The session key 9d8c7b6a5e4f3d2c1b0a9e8f7d6c5b4a was logged from IPv4 10.0.0.2 on 2024-08-15 at Paris office.,"[(16, 52, 'Token keys'), (70, 79, 'IP-Address'), (83, 93, 'DATE'), (97, 103, 'LOC')]"
Token f0e1d2c3b4a5968778695a4b3c2d1e0f authorized access from IP 192.168.1.50 on 2024-09-10 at New York data center.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (51, 66, 'IP-Address'), (70, 80, 'DATE'), (84, 104, 'LOC')]"
User session token aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 was initiated from IPv6 2607:f8b0:4005:805::200e on 2024-10-25 in Seattle by developer Mike Ross.,"[(13, 49, 'Token keys'), (58, 85, 'IP-Address'), (89, 99, 'DATE'), (103, 110, 'LOC'), (114, 124, 'PER')]"
Token 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef failed login from IP 172.16.254.1 on 2024-11-05 at London branch.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (64, 75, 'IP-Address'), (79, 89, 'DATE'), (93, 99, 'LOC')]"
The encryption token 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788796a5b4c3d2e1f0a was used from IPv4 198.51.100.2 on 2024-12-20 at Berlin office.,"[(19, 55, 'Token keys'), (73, 88, 'IP-Address'), (92, 102, 'DATE'), (106, 112, 'LOC')]"
Token 9a8b7c6d5e4f3a2b1c0d9e8f7b6a5c4d was authorized from IP 10.10.1.1 on 2024-01-15 at San Francisco headquarters.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (51, 60, 'IP-Address'), (64, 74, 'DATE'), (78, 99, 'LOC')]"
Access token ffeeddccbbaa99887766554433221100 was generated from IPv6 fe80::1ff:fe23:4567:890a on 2024-02-28 at Tokyo branch by admin Rachel Green.,"[(13, 49, 'Token keys'), (68, 87, 'IP-Address'), (91, 101, 'DATE'), (105, 111, 'LOC'), (115, 127, 'PER')]"
Token aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 was revoked after suspicious login from IP 192.168.100.100 on 2024-03-15 at New York office.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (76, 91, 'IP-Address'), (95, 105, 'DATE'), (109, 121, 'LOC')]"
User token 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef was created from IPv4 203.0.113.10 on 2024-04-10 in London by technician Ross Geller.,"[(11, 47, 'Token keys'), (56, 68, 'IP-Address'), (72, 82, 'DATE'), (86, 92, 'LOC'), (96, 108, 'PER')]"
The session key 9d8c7b6a5e4f3d2c1b0a9e8f7d6c5b4a was logged from IP 172.20.10.5 on 2024-05-05 at Paris data center.,"[(16, 52, 'Token keys'), (61, 72, 'IP-Address'), (76, 86, 'DATE'), (90, 106, 'LOC')]"
Token f0e1d2c3b4a5968778695a4b3c2d1e0f authorized access from IPv6 2607:f8b0:4005:805::200e on 2024-06-15 at Berlin headquarters.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (70, 98, 'IP-Address'), (102, 112, 'DATE'), (116, 126, 'LOC')]"
User session token aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 was initiated from IP 10.10.10.10 on 2024-07-20 in Tokyo by developer Monica Geller.,"[(13, 49, 'Token keys'), (58, 69, 'IP-Address'), (73, 83, 'DATE'), (87, 92, 'LOC'), (96, 110, 'PER')]"
Token 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef failed login from IPv4 198.51.100.100 on 2024-08-05 at San Francisco office.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (60, 75, 'IP-Address'), (79, 89, 'DATE'), (93, 108, 'LOC')]"
The encryption token 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788796a5b4c3d2e1f0a was used from IP 192.168.1.1 on 2024-09-15 at London headquarters.,"[(19, 55, 'Token keys'), (64, 75, 'IP-Address'), (79, 89, 'DATE'), (93, 113, 'LOC')]"
Token 9a8b7c6d5e4f3a2b1c0d9e8f7b6a5c4d was authorized from IPv6 fe80::f2de:f1ff:fe3f:307e on 2024-10-10 at New York branch.,"[(6, 42, 'Token keys'), (70, 88, 'IP-Address'), (92, 102, 'DATE'), (106, 114, 'LOC')]"
Access token ffeeddccbbaa99887766554433221100 was generated from IP 172.16.0.1 on 2024-11-25 at Paris office by admin Chandler Bing.,"[(13, 49, 'Token keys'), (58, 69, 'IP-Address'), (73, 83, 'DATE'), (87, 97, 'LOC'), (101, 114, 'PER')]"
User token aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 was created from IPv4 203.0.113.1 on 2024-12-05 in Berlin by developer Rachel Adams.,"[(11, 47, 'Token keys'), (56, 68, 'IP-Address'), (72, 82, 'DATE'), (86, 92, 'LOC'), (96, 110, 'PER')]"
"User John Doe accessed the server at 192.168.1.45 using token key a3f9b7d6e1c24f8b9d0e7a6c5b3f2d1e on April 5, 2023.","[(5, 13, 'PER'), (39, 51, 'IP-Address'), (66, 102, 'Token keys'), (106, 116, 'DATE')]"
The database backup was completed on 2024-01-10 from IP 2001:0db8:85a3:0000:0000:8a2e:0370:7334 with access token 9f8e7d6c5b4a392018facbde76e54321.,"[(46, 56, 'DATE'), (62, 101, 'IP-Address'), (113, 145, 'Token keys')]"
Administrator Alice logged in from IP 10.0.0.254 using the token key 4e5d6c7b8a9f0123456789abcdef1234 on March 3rd.,"[(14, 19, 'PER'), (34, 43, 'IP-Address'), (61, 97, 'Token keys'), (101, 110, 'DATE')]"
New purchase order #4578 was created by Bob Smith on 172.16.254.1 with session token z9y8x7w6v5u4t3s2r1q0p9o8n7m6l5k4.,"[(20, 24, 'CARDINAL'), (38, 47, 'PER'), (51, 62, 'IP-Address'), (77, 113, 'Token keys')]"
The server located in Berlin responded to request from 203.0.113.195 with token key ab12cd34ef56gh78ij90kl12mn34op56 at 12:00 PM.,"[(22, 28, 'LOC'), (54, 65, 'IP-Address'), (81, 117, 'Token keys'), (121, 129, 'DATE')]"
Client María used token key 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef to connect from IPv6 address fe80::1ff:fe23:4567:890a on 15th June.,"[(7, 12, 'PER'), (23, 55, 'Token keys'), (74, 93, 'IP-Address'), (97, 106, 'DATE')]"
Update pushed to repository GitHub by user Charlie on 10.10.2023 from IP 8.8.8.8 with token key fedcba9876543210fedcba9876543210.,"[(27, 33, 'ORG'), (37, 44, 'PER'), (48, 58, 'DATE'), (64, 69, 'IP-Address'), (81, 117, 'Token keys')]"
Payment of $499.99 was authorized by company Acme Corp from IP 192.0.2.146 using token key 0a1b2c3d4e5f6789abcdef0123456789 on 2023-12-01.,"[(11, 17, 'MONEY'), (40, 49, 'ORG'), (55, 66, 'IP-Address'), (81, 117, 'Token keys'), (121, 131, 'DATE')]"
Developer Ling submitted code commit with token key aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 from IP 172.31.255.255 on Friday.,"[(10, 14, 'PER'), (45, 81, 'Token keys'), (87, 99, 'IP-Address'), (103, 110, 'DATE')]"
Server at location Tokyo received request from IP 203.0.113.1; authentication token: 1234abcd5678efgh9012ijkl3456mnop.,"[(21, 26, 'LOC'), (50, 61, 'IP-Address'), (79, 115, 'Token keys')]"
"On 2023-07-20, user David accessed resource on IP 10.10.10.10 using token key 9876543210abcdef9876543210abcdef.","[(3, 13, 'DATE'), (19, 24, 'PER'), (47, 57, 'IP-Address'), (73, 109, 'Token keys')]"
The language setting was changed to Spanish by admin from IP 2400:cb00:2048:1::c629:d7a2 using token key a1b2c3d4e5f60718293a4b5c6d7e8f9a.,"[(22, 29, 'LANGUAGE'), (44, 49, 'PER'), (55, 80, 'IP-Address'), (93, 129, 'Token keys')]"
Backup completed on 01-05-2024 from server 192.168.100.100 with token key deadbeefcafebabe1234567890abcdef.,"[(17, 27, 'DATE'), (33, 48, 'IP-Address'), (59, 95, 'Token keys')]"
Employee Sarah sent an email from IP 198.51.100.23 using token key 00112233445566778899aabbccddeeff on 2nd February.,"[(9, 14, 'PER'), (35, 48, 'IP-Address'), (64, 100, 'Token keys'), (104, 118, 'DATE')]"
The work 'The Art of Computer Programming' was accessed by user Alan from IP 127.0.0.1 with token key 123abc456def7890abc123def4567890.,"[(9, 41, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (56, 60, 'PER'), (66, 77, 'IP-Address'), (91, 127, 'Token keys')]"
Session started by user Emily on 255.255.255.255 with token key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788776655443322110 at 09:30.,"[(21, 26, 'PER'), (30, 41, 'IP-Address'), (57, 93, 'Token keys'), (97, 102, 'DATE')]"
The server in New York responded to token key 11223344556677889900aabbccddeeff from IP 10.1.1.1 during maintenance.,"[(14, 22, 'LOC'), (41, 77, 'Token keys'), (83, 92, 'IP-Address')]"
User Iván logged in on 2022-11-11 from IPv6 address 2001:db8::ff00:42:8329 using token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890.,"[(5, 9, 'PER'), (19, 29, 'DATE'), (45, 63, 'IP-Address'), (79, 115, 'Token keys')]"
Order #1234 worth $1500 was processed on IP 192.0.2.44 with token key 99887766554433221100ffeeddccbbaa.,"[(6, 10, 'CARDINAL'), (17, 22, 'MONEY'), (39, 50, 'IP-Address'), (64, 100, 'Token keys')]"
The document 'Network Architecture' was edited by user Zoe at IP 203.0.113.77 using token key 0a0b0c0d0e0f10111213141516171819.,"[(13, 33, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (51, 54, 'PER'), (58, 70, 'IP-Address'), (84, 120, 'Token keys')]"
New user registration: Michael from IP 172.20.10.5 with token key deadbeef1234567890abcdefdeadbeef on 2024-06-15.,"[(18, 25, 'PER'), (31, 43, 'IP-Address'), (58, 94, 'Token keys'), (98, 108, 'DATE')]"
Payment of $249.99 received from client Acme Inc at IP 198.51.100.99 using token key 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef.,"[(11, 17, 'MONEY'), (36, 44, 'ORG'), (48, 60, 'IP-Address'), (75, 111, 'Token keys')]"
The firmware version 3.14 was updated on device with IP 10.10.0.1 using token key 1a2b3c4d5e6f77889900aabbccddeeff.,"[(19, 22, 'CARDINAL'), (45, 54, 'IP-Address'), (68, 104, 'Token keys')]"
User Emma accessed the system from IP 192.168.0.101 with token key 1122aabb3344ccdd5566eeff77889900 on Monday.,"[(5, 9, 'PER'), (38, 51, 'IP-Address'), (65, 101, 'Token keys'), (105, 111, 'DATE')]"
Server log shows connection from IP 2001:db8:85a3::8a2e:370:7334 using token key abc123def456ghi789jkl012mno345pq.,"[(31, 56, 'IP-Address'), (71, 107, 'Token keys')]"
Client with ID 7890 connected from IP 203.0.113.10 using token key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788776655443322110 on 11/11/2023.,"[(15, 19, 'CARDINAL'), (39, 50, 'IP-Address'), (64, 100, 'Token keys'), (104, 114, 'DATE')]"
The research paper 'Quantum Computing Advances' was accessed by Dr. Smith at IP 172.16.0.2 with token key 123abc456def7890abc123def4567890.,"[(20, 48, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (62, 70, 'PER'), (74, 85, 'IP-Address'), (99, 135, 'Token keys')]"
User Liam logged in from IPv6 address fe80::abcd:1234:5678:9abc using token key fedcba9876543210fedcba9876543210 on 2023-08-25.,"[(5, 9, 'PER'), (30, 54, 'IP-Address'), (70, 106, 'Token keys'), (110, 120, 'DATE')]"
The payment of $350 was received from organization Globex at IP 192.0.2.1 using token key aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899.,"[(16, 20, 'MONEY'), (45, 51, 'ORG'), (55, 66, 'IP-Address'), (80, 116, 'Token keys')]"
System alert: user Oliver accessed from IP 10.0.0.15 with token key 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef on 5th May.,"[(14, 20, 'PER'), (34, 43, 'IP-Address'), (59, 95, 'Token keys'), (99, 106, 'DATE')]"
The novel 'Invisible Cities' was read by Laura from IP 198.51.100.45 using token key deadbeefcafebabe1234567890abcdef.,"[(10, 27, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (37, 42, 'PER'), (46, 58, 'IP-Address'), (72, 108, 'Token keys')]"
"On 2023-03-17, user Ethan accessed the platform from IPv6 address 2001:0db8:85a3::8a2e:0370:7334 with token key 0a1b2c3d4e5f60718293a4b5c6d7e8f9a.","[(3, 13, 'DATE'), (19, 24, 'PER'), (58, 76, 'IP-Address'), (92, 128, 'Token keys')]"
The IP address 172.16.254.254 was blocked after token key 9f8e7d6c5b4a392018facbde76e54321 was detected on 12/12/2023.,"[(13, 26, 'IP-Address'), (44, 80, 'Token keys'), (94, 104, 'DATE')]"
User Sophia updated settings from IP 192.168.10.10 using token key 4e5d6c7b8a9f0123456789abcdef1234 on Tuesday.,"[(5, 11, 'PER'), (34, 46, 'IP-Address'), (62, 98, 'Token keys'), (102, 109, 'DATE')]"
The language Python was selected by user James from IP 203.0.113.5 with token key fedcba9876543210fedcba9876543210.,"[(13, 19, 'LANGUAGE'), (38, 43, 'PER'), (47, 58, 'IP-Address'), (72, 108, 'Token keys')]"
Update applied on 2023-09-30 from server 10.0.0.5 with token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890.,"[(17, 27, 'DATE'), (34, 43, 'IP-Address'), (57, 93, 'Token keys')]"
User Olivia logged in from IP 198.51.100.100 using token key 11223344556677889900aabbccddeeff on Sunday.,"[(5, 11, 'PER'), (30, 43, 'IP-Address'), (59, 95, 'Token keys'), (99, 105, 'DATE')]"
The server in London received request from IPv6 address fe80::1ff:fe23:4567:890a with token key 1234abcd5678efgh9012ijkl3456mnop.,"[(14, 20, 'LOC'), (49, 67, 'IP-Address'), (81, 117, 'Token keys')]"
Client number 6789 connected from IP 172.31.0.1 using token key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788776655443322110 on 2023-07-04.,"[(14, 18, 'CARDINAL'), (38, 48, 'IP-Address'), (62, 98, 'Token keys'), (102, 112, 'DATE')]"
The document 'Deep Learning Revolution' was accessed by user Mia at IP 10.10.10.10 with token key 9876543210abcdef9876543210abcdef.,"[(13, 38, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (56, 59, 'PER'), (63, 73, 'IP-Address'), (87, 123, 'Token keys')]"
User Noah logged in from IPv6 address 2001:db8::ff00:42:8329 using token key deadbeef1234567890abcdefdeadbeef on 2023-11-11.,"[(5, 9, 'PER'), (30, 48, 'IP-Address'), (64, 100, 'Token keys'), (104, 114, 'DATE')]"
Payment of $1200 was received from company Initech at IP 192.0.2.255 using token key aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899.,"[(11, 16, 'MONEY'), (41, 48, 'ORG'), (52, 63, 'IP-Address'), (77, 113, 'Token keys')]"
System alert: user Ava accessed from IP 10.0.0.25 with token key 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef on 6th June.,"[(14, 17, 'PER'), (31, 40, 'IP-Address'), (56, 92, 'Token keys'), (96, 104, 'DATE')]"
The novel 'The Great Gatsby' was read by user Ethan from IP 198.51.100.50 using token key deadbeefcafebabe1234567890abcdef.,"[(10, 27, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (41, 46, 'PER'), (50, 62, 'IP-Address'), (76, 112, 'Token keys')]"
"On 2023-05-05, user Lily accessed the platform from IPv6 address 2001:0db8:85a3::8a2e:0370:7334 with token key 0a1b2c3d4e5f60718293a4b5c6d7e8f9a.","[(3, 13, 'DATE'), (19, 23, 'PER'), (57, 75, 'IP-Address'), (91, 127, 'Token keys')]"
The IP 172.16.254.253 was blocked after token key 9f8e7d6c5b4a392018facbde76e54321 was detected on 01/01/2024.,"[(7, 20, 'IP-Address'), (38, 74, 'Token keys'), (88, 98, 'DATE')]"
User Grace updated settings from IP 192.168.10.11 using token key 4e5d6c7b8a9f0123456789abcdef1234 on Wednesday.,"[(5, 10, 'PER'), (33, 46, 'IP-Address'), (62, 98, 'Token keys'), (102, 111, 'DATE')]"
The programming language JavaScript was selected by user Jack from IP 203.0.113.6 with token key fedcba9876543210fedcba9876543210.,"[(24, 34, 'LANGUAGE'), (53, 57, 'PER'), (61, 72, 'IP-Address'), (86, 122, 'Token keys')]"
Firmware version 4.5 was updated on device with IP 10.0.0.6 using token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890.,"[(17, 20, 'CARDINAL'), (43, 52, 'IP-Address'), (66, 102, 'Token keys')]"
User Mia accessed the system from IP 192.168.0.102 with token key 1122aabb3344ccdd5566eeff77889900 on Thursday.,"[(5, 8, 'PER'), (37, 50, 'IP-Address'), (64, 100, 'Token keys'), (104, 112, 'DATE')]"
Server log shows connection from IP 2001:db8:85a3::8a2e:370:7335 using token key abc123def456ghi789jkl012mno345pq.,"[(31, 56, 'IP-Address'), (71, 107, 'Token keys')]"
Client with ID 7891 connected from IP 203.0.113.11 using token key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788776655443322110 on 12/12/2023.,"[(15, 19, 'CARDINAL'), (39, 50, 'IP-Address'), (64, 100, 'Token keys'), (104, 114, 'DATE')]"
The research paper 'AI and Society' was accessed by Dr. Parker at IP 172.16.0.3 with token key 123abc456def7890abc123def4567890.,"[(20, 35, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (49, 59, 'PER'), (63, 74, 'IP-Address'), (88, 124, 'Token keys')]"
User Mia logged in from IPv6 address fe80::abcd:1234:5678:9abd using token key fedbeef9876543210fedcba9876543210 on 2023-11-12.,"[(5, 8, 'PER'), (29, 53, 'IP-Address'), (69, 105, 'Token keys'), (109, 119, 'DATE')]"
Payment of $1250 was received from company Starlight at IP 192.0.2.256 using token key aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899.,"[(11, 16, 'MONEY'), (41, 50, 'ORG'), (54, 65, 'IP-Address'), (79, 115, 'Token keys')]"
System alert: user Zoe accessed from IP 10.0.0.26 with token key 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef on 7th July.,"[(14, 17, 'PER'), (31, 40, 'IP-Address'), (56, 92, 'Token keys'), (96, 105, 'DATE')]"
The novel 'To Kill a Mockingbird' was read by user Liam from IP 198.51.100.51 using token key deadbeefcafebabe1234567890abcdef.,"[(10, 33, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (41, 45, 'PER'), (49, 61, 'IP-Address'), (75, 111, 'Token keys')]"
"On 2023-05-06, user Ava accessed the platform from IPv6 address 2001:0db8:85a3::8a2e:0370:7335 with token key 0a1b2c3d4e5f60718293a4b5c6d7e8f9a.","[(3, 13, 'DATE'), (19, 22, 'PER'), (57, 75, 'IP-Address'), (91, 127, 'Token keys')]"
The IP 172.16.254.252 was blocked after token key 9f8e7d6c5b4a392018facbde76e54321 was detected on 02/01/2024.,"[(7, 20, 'IP-Address'), (38, 74, 'Token keys'), (88, 98, 'DATE')]"
User Grace updated settings from IP 192.168.10.12 using token key 4e5d6c7b8a9f0123456789abcdef1234 on Thursday.,"[(5, 10, 'PER'), (33, 46, 'IP-Address'), (62, 98, 'Token keys'), (102, 110, 'DATE')]"
The programming language Ruby was selected by user Jack from IP 203.0.113.7 with token key fedcba9876543210fedcba9876543210.,"[(24, 28, 'LANGUAGE'), (53, 57, 'PER'), (61, 72, 'IP-Address'), (86, 122, 'Token keys')]"
Firmware version 4.6 was updated on device with IP 10.0.0.7 using token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890.,"[(17, 20, 'CARDINAL'), (43, 52, 'IP-Address'), (66, 102, 'Token keys')]"
User Mia accessed the system from IP 192.168.0.103 with token key 1122aabb3344ccdd5566eeff77889900 on Friday.,"[(5, 8, 'PER'), (37, 50, 'IP-Address'), (64, 100, 'Token keys'), (104, 110, 'DATE')]"
Server log shows connection from IP 2001:db8:85a3::8a2e:370:7336 using token key abc123def456ghi789jkl012mno345pq.,"[(31, 56, 'IP-Address'), (71, 107, 'Token keys')]"
Client with ID 7892 connected from IP 203.0.113.12 using token key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788776655443322110 on 13/12/2023.,"[(15, 19, 'CARDINAL'), (39, 50, 'IP-Address'), (64, 100, 'Token keys'), (104, 114, 'DATE')]"
The research paper 'Machine Learning Basics' was accessed by Dr. Lee at IP 172.16.0.4 with token key 123abc456def7890abc123def4567890.,"[(20, 45, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (49, 56, 'PER'), (60, 71, 'IP-Address'), (85, 121, 'Token keys')]"
User Mia logged in from IPv6 address fe80::abcd:1234:5678:9abe using token key fedbeef9876543210fedcba9876543210 on 2023-11-13.,"[(5, 8, 'PER'), (29, 53, 'IP-Address'), (69, 105, 'Token keys'), (109, 119, 'DATE')]"
Payment of $1300 was received from company SunTech at IP 192.0.2.257 using token key aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899.,"[(11, 16, 'MONEY'), (41, 48, 'ORG'), (52, 63, 'IP-Address'), (77, 113, 'Token keys')]"
System alert: user Zoe accessed from IP 10.0.0.27 with token key 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef on 8th August.,"[(14, 17, 'PER'), (31, 40, 'IP-Address'), (56, 92, 'Token keys'), (96, 106, 'DATE')]"
The novel '1984' was read by user Liam from IP 198.51.100.52 using token key deadbeefcafebabe1234567890abcdef.,"[(10, 14, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (28, 32, 'PER'), (36, 48, 'IP-Address'), (62, 98, 'Token keys')]"
"On 2023-05-07, user Ava accessed the platform from IPv6 address 2001:0db8:85a3::8a2e:0370:7336 with token key 0a1b2c3d4e5f60718293a4b5c6d7e8f9a.","[(3, 13, 'DATE'), (19, 22, 'PER'), (57, 75, 'IP-Address'), (91, 127, 'Token keys')]"
The IP 172.16.254.251 was blocked after token key 9f8e7d6c5b4a392018facbde76e54321 was detected on 03/01/2024.,"[(7, 20, 'IP-Address'), (38, 74, 'Token keys'), (88, 98, 'DATE')]"
User Grace updated settings from IP 192.168.10.13 using token key 4e5d6c7b8a9f0123456789abcdef1234 on Friday.,"[(5, 10, 'PER'), (33, 46, 'IP-Address'), (62, 98, 'Token keys'), (102, 108, 'DATE')]"
The programming language Go was selected by user Jack from IP 203.0.113.8 with token key fedcba9876543210fedcba9876543210.,"[(24, 26, 'LANGUAGE'), (53, 57, 'PER'), (61, 72, 'IP-Address'), (86, 122, 'Token keys')]"
Firmware version 4.7 was updated on device with IP 10.0.0.8 using token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890.,"[(17, 20, 'CARDINAL'), (43, 52, 'IP-Address'), (66, 102, 'Token keys')]"
User Mia accessed the system from IP 192.168.0.104 with token key 1122aabb3344ccdd5566eeff77889900 on Saturday.,"[(5, 8, 'PER'), (37, 50, 'IP-Address'), (64, 100, 'Token keys'), (104, 112, 'DATE')]"
Server log shows connection from IP 2001:db8:85a3::8a2e:370:7337 using token key abc123def456ghi789jkl012mno345pq.,"[(31, 56, 'IP-Address'), (71, 107, 'Token keys')]"
Client with ID 7893 connected from IP 203.0.113.13 using token key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788776655443322110 on 14/12/2023.,"[(15, 19, 'CARDINAL'), (39, 50, 'IP-Address'), (64, 100, 'Token keys'), (104, 114, 'DATE')]"
The research paper 'Data Science Today' was accessed by Dr. Kim at IP 172.16.0.5 with token key 123abc456def7890abc123def4567890.,"[(20, 40, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (44, 50, 'PER'), (54, 65, 'IP-Address'), (79, 115, 'Token keys')]"
User Mia logged in from IPv6 address fe80::abcd:1234:5678:9abf using token key fedbeef9876543210fedcba9876543210 on 2023-11-14.,"[(5, 8, 'PER'), (29, 53, 'IP-Address'), (69, 105, 'Token keys'), (109, 119, 'DATE')]"
Payment of $1350 was received from company NovaTech at IP 192.0.2.258 using token key aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899.,"[(11, 16, 'MONEY'), (41, 49, 'ORG'), (53, 64, 'IP-Address'), (78, 114, 'Token keys')]"
System alert: user Zoe accessed from IP 10.0.0.28 with token key 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef on 9th September.,"[(14, 17, 'PER'), (31, 40, 'IP-Address'), (56, 92, 'Token keys'), (96, 108, 'DATE')]"
The novel 'Brave New World' was read by user Liam from IP 198.51.100.53 using token key deadbeefcafebabe1234567890abcdef.,"[(10, 27, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (41, 45, 'PER'), (49, 61, 'IP-Address'), (75, 111, 'Token keys')]"
"On 2023-05-08, user Ava accessed the platform from IPv6 address 2001:0db8:85a3::8a2e:0370:7337 with token key 0a1b2c3d4e5f60718293a4b5c6d7e8f9a.","[(3, 13, 'DATE'), (19, 22, 'PER'), (57, 75, 'IP-Address'), (91, 127, 'Token keys')]"
The IP 172.16.254.250 was blocked after token key 9f8e7d6c5b4a392018facbde76e54321 was detected on 04/01/2024.,"[(7, 20, 'IP-Address'), (38, 74, 'Token keys'), (88, 98, 'DATE')]"
User Grace updated settings from IP 192.168.10.14 using token key 4e5d6c7b8a9f0123456789abcdef1234 on Saturday.,"[(5, 10, 'PER'), (33, 46, 'IP-Address'), (62, 98, 'Token keys'), (102, 110, 'DATE')]"
The programming language Swift was selected by user Jack from IP 203.0.113.9 with token key fedcba9876543210fedcba9876543210.,"[(24, 29, 'LANGUAGE'), (53, 57, 'PER'), (61, 72, 'IP-Address'), (86, 122, 'Token keys')]"
Firmware version 4.8 was updated on device with IP 10.0.0.9 using token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890.,"[(17, 20, 'CARDINAL'), (43, 52, 'IP-Address'), (66, 102, 'Token keys')]"
User Mia accessed the system from IP 192.168.0.105 with token key 1122aabb3344ccdd5566eeff77889900 on Sunday.,"[(5, 8, 'PER'), (37, 50, 'IP-Address'), (64, 100, 'Token keys'), (104, 110, 'DATE')]"
Server log shows connection from IP 2001:db8:85a3::8a2e:370:7338 using token key abc123def456ghi789jkl012mno345pq.,"[(31, 56, 'IP-Address'), (71, 107, 'Token keys')]"
Client with ID 7894 connected from IP 203.0.113.14 using token key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788776655443322110 on 15/12/2023.,"[(15, 19, 'CARDINAL'), (39, 50, 'IP-Address'), (64, 100, 'Token keys'), (104, 114, 'DATE')]"
The research paper 'Blockchain Basics' was accessed by Dr. Wang at IP 172.16.0.6 with token key 123abc456def7890abc123def4567890.,"[(20, 39, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (43, 49, 'PER'), (53, 64, 'IP-Address'), (78, 114, 'Token keys')]"
User Mia logged in from IPv6 address fe80::abcd:1234:5678:9ac0 using token key fedbeef9876543210fedcba9876543210 on 2023-11-15.,"[(5, 8, 'PER'), (29, 53, 'IP-Address'), (69, 105, 'Token keys'), (109, 119, 'DATE')]"
Payment of $1400 was received from company Cyberdyne at IP 192.0.2.259 using token key aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899.,"[(11, 16, 'MONEY'), (41, 50, 'ORG'), (54, 65, 'IP-Address'), (79, 115, 'Token keys')]"
System alert: user Zoe accessed from IP 10.0.0.29 with token key 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef on 10th October.,"[(14, 17, 'PER'), (31, 40, 'IP-Address'), (56, 92, 'Token keys'), (96, 108, 'DATE')]"
The novel 'Catch-22' was read by user Liam from IP 198.51.100.54 using token key deadbeefcafebabe1234567890abcdef.,"[(10, 18, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (28, 32, 'PER'), (36, 48, 'IP-Address'), (62, 98, 'Token keys')]"
"On 2023-05-09, user Ava accessed the platform from IPv6 address 2001:0db8:85a3::8a2e:0370:7338 with token key 0a1b2c3d4e5f60718293a4b5c6d7e8f9a.","[(3, 13, 'DATE'), (19, 22, 'PER'), (57, 75, 'IP-Address'), (91, 127, 'Token keys')]"
The IP 172.16.254.249 was blocked after token key 9f8e7d6c5b4a392018facbde76e54321 was detected on 05/01/2024.,"[(7, 20, 'IP-Address'), (38, 74, 'Token keys'), (88, 98, 'DATE')]"
User Grace updated settings from IP 192.168.10.15 using token key 4e5d6c7b8a9f0123456789abcdef1234 on Sunday.,"[(5, 10, 'PER'), (33, 46, 'IP-Address'), (62, 98, 'Token keys'), (102, 108, 'DATE')]"
The programming language Kotlin was selected by user Jack from IP 203.0.113.10 with token key fedcba9876543210fedcba9876543210.,"[(24, 30, 'LANGUAGE'), (53, 57, 'PER'), (61, 72, 'IP-Address'), (86, 122, 'Token keys')]"
"User token 9f8d7a6b5c4e3f2a1b0c detected from IP 192.168.1.45 during login at 2024-04-15, triggering alert for 5 failed attempts at Acme Corp.","[(11, 31, 'Token keys'), (45, 56, 'IP-Address'), (72, 82, 'DATE'), (105, 106, 'CARDINAL'), (110, 119, 'ORG')]"
The device with token key a1b2c3d4e5f67890abcdef12 connected from IPv6 address 2001:0db8:85a3:0000:0000:8a2e:0370:7334 on 2023-11-02 at Berlin office.,"[(20, 44, 'Token keys'), (66, 105, 'IP-Address'), (109, 119, 'DATE'), (123, 129, 'LOC')]"
"Transaction authorized using token key ffeeddccbbaa99887766554433221100 from IP 10.0.0.15 for $1,250 at 1st National Bank on 01/12/2024.","[(31, 63, 'Token keys'), (69, 77, 'IP-Address'), (83, 88, 'MONEY'), (92, 103, 'ORG'), (107, 117, 'DATE'), (122, 125, 'ORDINAL')]"
"New user created with token key 123abc456def789ghi012jkl345mno678 from IP 172.16.254.1 accessing the system on July 20, 2023 using English language settings.","[(23, 63, 'Token keys'), (69, 80, 'IP-Address'), (108, 120, 'DATE'), (126, 133, 'LANGUAGE')]"
Backup completed at 2024-03-30 using token key 0a1b2c3d4e5f6789abcdef0123456789 from IP 8.8.8.8 with a size of 250 GB at Amazon Web Services.,"[(22, 32, 'DATE'), (39, 71, 'Token keys'), (77, 82, 'IP-Address'), (100, 104, 'QUANTITY'), (108, 129, 'ORG')]"
Alert: Token key 9a8b7c6d5e4f3g2h1i0jklmnopqrstuv from IP 123.45.67.89 reported 3 unauthorized login attempts on 2024-05-10 at Google headquarters.,"[(7, 47, 'Token keys'), (53, 64, 'IP-Address'), (73, 74, 'CARDINAL'), (91, 101, 'DATE'), (105, 111, 'ORG'), (112, 123, 'LOC')]"
"Server at 10.10.10.10 generated new token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890 on 12/25/2023, processing 1500 requests in total, hosted by OpenAI.","[(10, 20, 'IP-Address'), (39, 71, 'Token keys'), (75, 85, 'DATE'), (96, 100, 'CARDINAL'), (119, 125, 'ORG')]"
The update package version 3.2.1 was downloaded on 2023-08-01 using token key deadbeefcafebabe1234567890abcdef from IP 2001:4860:4860::8888.,"[(44, 54, 'DATE'), (61, 97, 'Token keys'), (103, 128, 'IP-Address'), (28, 33, 'MISC')]"
"Client with token key 11223344556677889900aabbccddeeff connected from IP 255.255.255.255 on 15-Mar-2024 at London data center, transferring 500 MB data.","[(19, 55, 'Token keys'), (71, 84, 'IP-Address'), (88, 99, 'DATE'), (103, 109, 'LOC'), (121, 124, 'QUANTITY'), (125, 128, 'MISC')]"
User Jane Doe authenticated with token key aa11bb22cc33dd44ee55ff6677889900 from IP fe80::1ff:fe23:4567:890a on 2024-01-15 at Microsoft.,"[(5, 13, 'PER'), (38, 74, 'Token keys'), (80, 102, 'IP-Address'), (106, 116, 'DATE'), (120, 129, 'ORG')]"
"Payment of $3,500 received on 2023-09-10 with transaction token key f1e2d3c4b5a697887766554433221100 from IP 192.0.2.146 by Stripe.","[(0, 7, 'MONEY'), (16, 26, 'DATE'), (46, 82, 'Token keys'), (88, 99, 'IP-Address'), (103, 109, 'ORG')]"
"Malware detected on 2024-02-28 at server with IP 172.217.3.110 using token key 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef, affecting 7 machines.","[(19, 29, 'DATE'), (44, 57, 'IP-Address'), (70, 106, 'Token keys'), (118, 119, 'CARDINAL')]"
The report titled 'Cybersecurity Trends 2024' was accessed on 01-15-2024 using token key aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 from IP 203.0.113.5.,"[(15, 40, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (54, 64, 'DATE'), (75, 111, 'Token keys'), (117, 128, 'IP-Address')]"
System reboot initiated by admin user with token key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788776655443322110 from IP 198.51.100.23 on 2024-06-10.,"[(36, 72, 'Token keys'), (78, 93, 'IP-Address'), (97, 107, 'DATE')]"
"New server provisioned on 2024-04-01 with IP 2607:f8b0:4005:805::200e and token key 99887766554433221100aabbccddeeff, located in Tokyo.","[(23, 33, 'DATE'), (39, 68, 'IP-Address'), (73, 109, 'Token keys'), (121, 126, 'LOC')]"
VPN access granted to user John Smith with token key aa99bb88cc77dd66ee55ff44aa33bb22 from IP 192.168.100.200 on 2024-05-22.,"[(19, 29, 'PER'), (50, 86, 'Token keys'), (92, 105, 'IP-Address'), (109, 119, 'DATE')]"
"Database backup of 1.5 TB completed at 2024-07-15 using token key 1234abcd5678efgh9012ijkl3456mnop from IP 10.11.12.13, managed by DataCorp.","[(20, 25, 'QUANTITY'), (37, 47, 'DATE'), (54, 90, 'Token keys'), (96, 105, 'IP-Address'), (117, 125, 'ORG')]"
Email sent from IP 172.31.0.5 with token key deadbeef1234567890abcdef12345678 on 2023-12-31 containing invoice of $450.,"[(16, 26, 'IP-Address'), (32, 68, 'Token keys'), (72, 82, 'DATE'), (105, 109, 'MONEY')]"
"Server load at 75% on 2024-03-05, token key fedcba9876543210fedcba9876543210 used from IP 8.8.4.4 at Google Cloud.","[(15, 18, 'QUANTITY'), (22, 32, 'DATE'), (34, 70, 'Token keys'), (81, 88, 'IP-Address'), (92, 103, 'ORG')]"
User authentication failed for token key a1b2c3d4e5f67890abcdef1234567890 from IP 192.0.2.1 on 2024-01-01 at Facebook HQ.,"[(32, 68, 'Token keys'), (74, 85, 'IP-Address'), (89, 99, 'DATE'), (103, 111, 'ORG'), (112, 115, 'MISC')]"
"Monthly report generated on 2024-02-10 for 3rd quarter, token key 0a0b0c0d0e0f1a1b1c1d1e1f2a2b2c2d from IP 192.168.0.100.","[(26, 36, 'DATE'), (41, 44, 'ORDINAL'), (46, 82, 'Token keys'), (88, 103, 'IP-Address')]"
API request received with token key 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef from IP 198.51.100.42 at 10:00 AM on 2024-06-01.,"[(25, 61, 'Token keys'), (67, 82, 'IP-Address'), (86, 102, 'DATE')]"
Security patch version 1.0 deployed on 2023-10-20 using token key abcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefabcdefabcd from IP fe80::1ff:fe23:4567:890a.,"[(23, 26, 'MISC'), (40, 50, 'DATE'), (56, 92, 'Token keys'), (98, 123, 'IP-Address')]"
User Maria Garcia logged in on 2024-05-05 from IP 203.0.113.10 with token key 11223344556677889900aabbccddeeff at Microsoft.,"[(5, 17, 'PER'), (31, 41, 'DATE'), (47, 60, 'IP-Address'), (66, 102, 'Token keys'), (106, 115, 'ORG')]"
Payment of $750 processed on 2024-04-18 using token key ffeeddccbbaa99887766554433221100 from IP 10.0.0.25 at PayPal.,"[(0, 6, 'MONEY'), (18, 28, 'DATE'), (35, 71, 'Token keys'), (77, 86, 'IP-Address'), (90, 96, 'ORG')]"
New device registered with token key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788776655443322110 from IP 192.168.1.100 on 2024-03-15 at Cisco Systems.,"[(27, 63, 'Token keys'), (69, 84, 'IP-Address'), (88, 98, 'DATE'), (102, 115, 'ORG')]"
"System outage reported on 2024-01-20 affecting 10 servers, token key aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 from IP 172.16.0.5.","[(22, 32, 'DATE'), (42, 44, 'CARDINAL'), (57, 93, 'Token keys'), (99, 110, 'IP-Address')]"
User token 1234abcd5678efgh9012ijkl3456mnop used to access IP 203.0.113.50 on 2024-07-01 at Netflix headquarters.,"[(11, 47, 'Token keys'), (62, 74, 'IP-Address'), (78, 88, 'DATE'), (92, 99, 'ORG'), (100, 111, 'LOC')]"
Login from IP 192.0.2.33 with token key deadbeefcafebabe1234567890abcdef detected on 2024-06-15 at IBM.,"[(11, 22, 'IP-Address'), (28, 64, 'Token keys'), (74, 84, 'DATE'), (88, 91, 'ORG')]"
Backup file of size 500 GB created on 2023-09-25 using token key 99887766554433221100aabbccddeeff from IP 10.10.10.10.,"[(16, 21, 'QUANTITY'), (31, 41, 'DATE'), (48, 84, 'Token keys'), (90, 100, 'IP-Address')]"
Alert triggered for user John Doe with token key a1b2c3d4e5f67890abcdef1234567890 from IP 198.51.100.42 on 2024-02-28.,"[(20, 28, 'PER'), (49, 85, 'Token keys'), (91, 106, 'IP-Address'), (110, 120, 'DATE')]"
Service restarted on 2024-03-10 at IP 2607:f8b0:4005:805::200e with token key 1234567890abcdef1234567890abcdef and processed 1000 requests.,"[(20, 30, 'DATE'), (34, 59, 'IP-Address'), (65, 101, 'Token keys'), (117, 121, 'CARDINAL')]"
"Invoice for $4,200 issued on 2023-11-11 with transaction token key ffeeddccbbaa99887766554433221100 from IP 203.0.113.7.","[(12, 18, 'MONEY'), (27, 37, 'DATE'), (56, 92, 'Token keys'), (98, 109, 'IP-Address')]"
User logged in from IP 192.168.0.1 on 2024-01-01 with token key aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 at Apple HQ.,"[(19, 30, 'IP-Address'), (34, 44, 'DATE'), (50, 86, 'Token keys'), (90, 95, 'ORG'), (96, 99, 'MISC')]"
New API token 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788776655443322110 generated for IP 172.16.254.1 on 2024-05-05 by GitHub.,"[(14, 50, 'Token keys'), (65, 76, 'IP-Address'), (80, 90, 'DATE'), (94, 100, 'ORG')]"
Failed login attempt 2 recorded on 2024-04-20 for token key 11223344556677889900aabbccddeeff coming from IP 10.0.0.5.,"[(24, 25, 'ORDINAL'), (37, 47, 'DATE'), (61, 97, 'Token keys'), (113, 122, 'IP-Address')]"
System update version 5.4 deployed on 2023-10-30 using token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890 from IP fe80::1ff:fe23:4567:890a.,"[(14, 17, 'MISC'), (31, 41, 'DATE'), (48, 84, 'Token keys'), (90, 115, 'IP-Address')]"
User Anna Lee accessed the system on 2024-06-01 from IP 198.51.100.99 with token key deadbeefcafebabe1234567890abcdef at Dropbox.,"[(5, 13, 'PER'), (42, 52, 'DATE'), (58, 71, 'IP-Address'), (77, 113, 'Token keys'), (117, 124, 'ORG')]"
"Payment of $5,000 processed on 2023-12-15 with token key 1234abcd5678efgh9012ijkl3456mnop from IP 203.0.113.11.","[(0, 7, 'MONEY'), (19, 29, 'DATE'), (38, 74, 'Token keys'), (80, 91, 'IP-Address')]"
Backup successful on 2024-02-01 using token key ffeeddccbbaa99887766554433221100 from IP 192.168.1.101 hosted by AWS.,"[(18, 28, 'DATE'), (35, 71, 'Token keys'), (77, 90, 'IP-Address'), (102, 105, 'ORG')]"
Unauthorized access detected on 2024-03-11 at IP 10.0.0.100 with token key aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 affecting 12 devices.,"[(29, 39, 'DATE'), (43, 54, 'IP-Address'), (60, 96, 'Token keys'), (107, 109, 'CARDINAL')]"
Report titled 'Network Security 2024' accessed on 01-20-2024 with token key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788776655443322110 from IP 198.51.100.24.,"[(15, 37, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (46, 56, 'DATE'), (67, 103, 'Token keys'), (109, 120, 'IP-Address')]"
User Michael Brown logged in on 2024-05-10 from IP 172.16.0.10 with token key 11223344556677889900aabbccddeeff at Oracle.,"[(5, 18, 'PER'), (32, 42, 'DATE'), (48, 61, 'IP-Address'), (67, 103, 'Token keys'), (107, 113, 'ORG')]"
"Payment of $3,250 received on 2023-11-05 with transaction token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890 from IP 203.0.113.15.","[(0, 7, 'MONEY'), (16, 26, 'DATE'), (45, 81, 'Token keys'), (87, 98, 'IP-Address')]"
"System rebooted on 2024-01-25 at IP 192.168.0.55 with token key deadbeefcafebabe1234567890abcdef, processing 2000 requests.","[(17, 27, 'DATE'), (31, 44, 'IP-Address'), (50, 86, 'Token keys'), (100, 104, 'CARDINAL')]"
VPN token aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 activated from IP 10.10.10.20 on 2024-04-10 at Dropbox.,"[(10, 46, 'Token keys'), (58, 71, 'IP-Address'), (75, 85, 'DATE'), (89, 96, 'ORG')]"
Database query executed on 2024-05-05 using token key 1234abcd5678efgh9012ijkl3456mnop from IP 172.31.0.6.,"[(24, 34, 'DATE'), (41, 77, 'Token keys'), (83, 94, 'IP-Address')]"
Failed login attempt 1 recorded on 2024-03-15 for token key ffeeddccbbaa99887766554433221100 coming from IP 192.168.1.200.,"[(24, 25, 'ORDINAL'), (37, 47, 'DATE'), (61, 97, 'Token keys'), (113, 127, 'IP-Address')]"
System update version 4.9 deployed on 2023-10-15 using token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890 from IP fe80::1ff:fe23:4567:890a.,"[(14, 17, 'MISC'), (31, 41, 'DATE'), (48, 84, 'Token keys'), (90, 115, 'IP-Address')]"
User Sarah Connor accessed the system on 2024-06-20 from IP 198.51.100.100 with token key deadbeefcafebabe1234567890abcdef at IBM.,"[(5, 17, 'PER'), (42, 52, 'DATE'), (58, 71, 'IP-Address'), (77, 113, 'Token keys'), (117, 120, 'ORG')]"
"Payment of $6,000 processed on 2023-12-20 with token key 1234abcd5678efgh9012ijkl3456mnop from IP 203.0.113.20.","[(0, 7, 'MONEY'), (19, 29, 'DATE'), (38, 74, 'Token keys'), (80, 91, 'IP-Address')]"
Backup successful on 2024-02-05 using token key ffeeddccbbaa99887766554433221100 from IP 192.168.1.105 hosted by AWS.,"[(18, 28, 'DATE'), (35, 71, 'Token keys'), (77, 90, 'IP-Address'), (102, 105, 'ORG')]"
Unauthorized access detected on 2024-03-20 at IP 10.0.0.105 with token key aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 affecting 15 devices.,"[(29, 39, 'DATE'), (43, 54, 'IP-Address'), (60, 96, 'Token keys'), (107, 109, 'CARDINAL')]"
Report titled 'Cloud Infrastructure 2024' accessed on 01-25-2024 with token key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788776655443322110 from IP 198.51.100.30.,"[(15, 40, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (49, 59, 'DATE'), (70, 106, 'Token keys'), (112, 123, 'IP-Address')]"
User David Kim logged in on 2024-05-15 from IP 172.16.0.15 with token key 11223344556677889900aabbccddeeff at Oracle.,"[(5, 14, 'PER'), (32, 42, 'DATE'), (48, 61, 'IP-Address'), (67, 103, 'Token keys'), (107, 113, 'ORG')]"
"Payment of $3,750 received on 2023-11-10 with transaction token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890 from IP 203.0.113.25.","[(0, 7, 'MONEY'), (16, 26, 'DATE'), (45, 81, 'Token keys'), (87, 98, 'IP-Address')]"
"System rebooted on 2024-01-30 at IP 192.168.0.60 with token key deadbeefcafebabe1234567890abcdef, processing 2500 requests.","[(17, 27, 'DATE'), (31, 44, 'IP-Address'), (50, 86, 'Token keys'), (100, 104, 'CARDINAL')]"
VPN token aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 activated from IP 10.10.10.25 on 2024-04-15 at Dropbox.,"[(10, 46, 'Token keys'), (58, 71, 'IP-Address'), (75, 85, 'DATE'), (89, 96, 'ORG')]"
Database query executed on 2024-05-10 using token key 1234abcd5678efgh9012ijkl3456mnop from IP 172.31.0.7.,"[(24, 34, 'DATE'), (41, 77, 'Token keys'), (83, 94, 'IP-Address')]"
Failed login attempt 3 recorded on 2024-03-20 for token key ffeeddccbbaa99887766554433221100 coming from IP 192.168.1.205.,"[(24, 25, 'ORDINAL'), (37, 47, 'DATE'), (61, 97, 'Token keys'), (113, 127, 'IP-Address')]"
System update version 4.10 deployed on 2023-10-20 using token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890 from IP fe80::1ff:fe23:4567:890a.,"[(14, 18, 'MISC'), (32, 42, 'DATE'), (49, 85, 'Token keys'), (91, 116, 'IP-Address')]"
User Linda Park accessed the system on 2024-06-25 from IP 198.51.100.110 with token key deadbeefcafebabe1234567890abcdef at IBM.,"[(5, 15, 'PER'), (43, 53, 'DATE'), (59, 72, 'IP-Address'), (78, 114, 'Token keys'), (118, 121, 'ORG')]"
"Payment of $6,500 processed on 2023-12-25 with token key 1234abcd5678efgh9012ijkl3456mnop from IP 203.0.113.30.","[(0, 7, 'MONEY'), (19, 29, 'DATE'), (38, 74, 'Token keys'), (80, 91, 'IP-Address')]"
Backup successful on 2024-02-10 using token key ffeeddccbbaa99887766554433221100 from IP 192.168.1.110 hosted by AWS.,"[(18, 28, 'DATE'), (35, 71, 'Token keys'), (77, 90, 'IP-Address'), (102, 105, 'ORG')]"
Unauthorized access detected on 2024-03-25 at IP 10.0.0.110 with token key aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 affecting 20 devices.,"[(29, 39, 'DATE'), (43, 54, 'IP-Address'), (60, 96, 'Token keys'), (107, 109, 'CARDINAL')]"
Report titled 'Data Analytics 2024' accessed on 01-30-2024 with token key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788776655443322110 from IP 198.51.100.40.,"[(15, 35, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (44, 54, 'DATE'), (65, 101, 'Token keys'), (107, 118, 'IP-Address')]"
User Kevin Lee logged in on 2024-05-20 from IP 172.16.0.20 with token key 11223344556677889900aabbccddeeff at Oracle.,"[(5, 14, 'PER'), (32, 42, 'DATE'), (48, 61, 'IP-Address'), (67, 103, 'Token keys'), (107, 113, 'ORG')]"
"Payment of $4,500 received on 2023-11-15 with transaction token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890 from IP 203.0.113.35.","[(0, 7, 'MONEY'), (16, 26, 'DATE'), (45, 81, 'Token keys'), (87, 98, 'IP-Address')]"
"System rebooted on 2024-01-31 at IP 192.168.0.65 with token key deadbeefcafebabe1234567890abcdef, processing 3000 requests.","[(17, 27, 'DATE'), (31, 44, 'IP-Address'), (50, 86, 'Token keys'), (100, 104, 'CARDINAL')]"
VPN token aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 activated from IP 10.10.10.30 on 2024-04-20 at Dropbox.,"[(10, 46, 'Token keys'), (58, 71, 'IP-Address'), (75, 85, 'DATE'), (89, 96, 'ORG')]"
Database query executed on 2024-05-15 using token key 1234abcd5678efgh9012ijkl3456mnop from IP 172.31.0.8.,"[(24, 34, 'DATE'), (41, 77, 'Token keys'), (83, 94, 'IP-Address')]"
Failed login attempt 4 recorded on 2024-03-25 for token key ffeeddccbbaa99887766554433221100 coming from IP 192.168.1.210.,"[(24, 25, 'ORDINAL'), (37, 47, 'DATE'), (61, 97, 'Token keys'), (113, 127, 'IP-Address')]"
System update version 4.11 deployed on 2023-10-25 using token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890 from IP fe80::1ff:fe23:4567:890a.,"[(14, 18, 'MISC'), (32, 42, 'DATE'), (49, 85, 'Token keys'), (91, 116, 'IP-Address')]"
User Emily Davis accessed the system on 2024-06-30 from IP 198.51.100.120 with token key deadbeefcafebabe1234567890abcdef at IBM.,"[(5, 16, 'PER'), (43, 53, 'DATE'), (59, 72, 'IP-Address'), (78, 114, 'Token keys'), (118, 121, 'ORG')]"
"Payment of $7,000 processed on 2023-12-30 with token key 1234abcd5678efgh9012ijkl3456mnop from IP 203.0.113.40.","[(0, 7, 'MONEY'), (19, 29, 'DATE'), (38, 74, 'Token keys'), (80, 91, 'IP-Address')]"
Backup successful on 2024-02-15 using token key ffeeddccbbaa99887766554433221100 from IP 192.168.1.115 hosted by AWS.,"[(18, 28, 'DATE'), (35, 71, 'Token keys'), (77, 90, 'IP-Address'), (102, 105, 'ORG')]"
Unauthorized access detected on 2024-03-30 at IP 10.0.0.115 with token key aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 affecting 25 devices.,"[(29, 39, 'DATE'), (43, 54, 'IP-Address'), (60, 96, 'Token keys'), (107, 109, 'CARDINAL')]"
Report titled 'AI Innovations 2024' accessed on 02-01-2024 with token key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788776655443322110 from IP 198.51.100.50.,"[(15, 33, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (42, 52, 'DATE'), (63, 99, 'Token keys'), (105, 116, 'IP-Address')]"
User Mark Thompson logged in on 2024-05-25 from IP 172.16.0.25 with token key 11223344556677889900aabbccddeeff at Oracle.,"[(5, 18, 'PER'), (32, 42, 'DATE'), (48, 61, 'IP-Address'), (67, 103, 'Token keys'), (107, 113, 'ORG')]"
"Payment of $4,800 received on 2023-11-20 with transaction token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890 from IP 203.0.113.45.","[(0, 7, 'MONEY'), (16, 26, 'DATE'), (45, 81, 'Token keys'), (87, 98, 'IP-Address')]"
"System rebooted on 2024-02-01 at IP 192.168.0.70 with token key deadbeefcafebabe1234567890abcdef, processing 3500 requests.","[(17, 27, 'DATE'), (31, 44, 'IP-Address'), (50, 86, 'Token keys'), (100, 104, 'CARDINAL')]"
VPN token aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 activated from IP 10.10.10.35 on 2024-04-25 at Dropbox.,"[(10, 46, 'Token keys'), (58, 71, 'IP-Address'), (75, 85, 'DATE'), (89, 96, 'ORG')]"
Database query executed on 2024-05-20 using token key 1234abcd5678efgh9012ijkl3456mnop from IP 172.31.0.9.,"[(24, 34, 'DATE'), (41, 77, 'Token keys'), (83, 94, 'IP-Address')]"
Failed login attempt 5 recorded on 2024-03-30 for token key ffeeddccbbaa99887766554433221100 coming from IP 192.168.1.215.,"[(24, 25, 'ORDINAL'), (37, 47, 'DATE'), (61, 97, 'Token keys'), (113, 127, 'IP-Address')]"
System update version 4.12 deployed on 2023-10-30 using token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890 from IP fe80::1ff:fe23:4567:890a.,"[(14, 18, 'MISC'), (32, 42, 'DATE'), (49, 85, 'Token keys'), (91, 116, 'IP-Address')]"
User Olivia Martinez accessed the system on 2024-07-05 from IP 198.51.100.130 with token key deadbeefcafebabe1234567890abcdef at IBM.,"[(5, 20, 'PER'), (43, 53, 'DATE'), (59, 72, 'IP-Address'), (78, 114, 'Token keys'), (118, 121, 'ORG')]"
"Payment of $7,500 processed on 2023-12-31 with token key 1234abcd5678efgh9012ijkl3456mnop from IP 203.0.113.50.","[(0, 7, 'MONEY'), (19, 29, 'DATE'), (38, 74, 'Token keys'), (80, 91, 'IP-Address')]"
Backup successful on 2024-02-20 using token key ffeeddccbbaa99887766554433221100 from IP 192.168.1.120 hosted by AWS.,"[(18, 28, 'DATE'), (35, 71, 'Token keys'), (77, 90, 'IP-Address'), (102, 105, 'ORG')]"
Unauthorized access detected on 2024-04-05 at IP 10.0.0.120 with token key aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 affecting 30 devices.,"[(29, 39, 'DATE'), (43, 54, 'IP-Address'), (60, 96, 'Token keys'), (107, 109, 'CARDINAL')]"
Report titled 'Quantum Computing 2024' accessed on 02-05-2024 with token key 0f1e2d3c4b5a69788776655443322110 from IP 198.51.100.60.,"[(15, 37, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (46, 56, 'DATE'), (67, 103, 'Token keys'), (109, 120, 'IP-Address')]"
User Ryan Walker logged in on 2024-05-30 from IP 172.16.0.30 with token key 11223344556677889900aabbccddeeff at Oracle.,"[(5, 16, 'PER'), (32, 42, 'DATE'), (48, 61, 'IP-Address'), (67, 103, 'Token keys'), (107, 113, 'ORG')]"
"Payment of $5,200 received on 2023-11-25 with transaction token key abcdef1234567890abcdef1234567890 from IP 203.0.113.55.","[(0, 7, 'MONEY'), (16, 26, 'DATE'), (45, 81, 'Token keys'), (87, 98, 'IP-Address')]"
"System rebooted on 2024-02-05 at IP 192.168.0.75 with token key deadbeefcafebabe1234567890abcdef, processing 4000 requests.","[(17, 27, 'DATE'), (31, 44, 'IP-Address'), (50, 86, 'Token keys'), (100, 104, 'CARDINAL')]"
VPN token aabbccddeeff00112233445566778899 activated from IP 10.10.10.40 on 2024-04-30 at Dropbox.,"[(10, 46, 'Token keys'), (58, 71, 'IP-Address'), (75, 85, 'DATE'), (89, 96, 'ORG')]"
Database query executed on 2024-05-25 using token key 1234abcd5678efgh9012ijkl3456mnop from IP 172.31.0.10.,"[(24, 34, 'DATE'), (41, 77, 'Token keys'), (83, 94, 'IP-Address')]"
Failed login attempt 6 recorded on 2024-04-05 for token key ffeeddccbbaa99887766554433221100 coming from IP 192.168.1.220.,"[(24, 25, 'ORDINAL'), (37, 47, 'DATE'), (61, 97, 'Token keys'), (113, 127, 'IP-Address')]"
User Alice reported an issue with server 192.168.1.45 and provided token key Z9X8Y7W6V5U4T3S2R1Q0P9O8N7M6L5K4 for verification on 2024-04-15.,"[(5, 10, 'PER'), (39, 51, 'IP-Address'), (70, 106, 'Token keys'), (120, 130, 'DATE')]"
"The patch KB5005565 was deployed on 10.10.10.10, using token key A1B2C3D4E5F60718293A4B5C6D7E8F90, improving performance by 15%.","[(10, 20, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (34, 43, 'IP-Address'), (56, 96, 'Token keys'), (104, 106, 'CARDINAL')]"
"Client Bob from New York contacted support, IP 2607:f0d0:1002:51::4, supplying token key 123ABC456DEF789GHI012JKL345MNO678.","[(7, 10, 'PER'), (15, 23, 'LOC'), (37, 56, 'IP-Address'), (72, 108, 'Token keys')]"
Invoice INV-2023-09-15 was generated for Acme Corp with IP 172.16.254.1 and token key 9F8E7D6C5B4A3210FEDCBA9876543210.,"[(8, 24, 'MISC'), (40, 49, 'ORG'), (55, 66, 'IP-Address'), (81, 113, 'Token keys'), (26, 36, 'DATE')]"
"Developer Chen pushed commit 3a4b5c6d to repo GitHub, IP 192.0.2.146 with token key ABCD1234EFGH5678IJKL9012MNOP3456.","[(10, 14, 'PER'), (33, 41, 'MISC'), (47, 59, 'ORG'), (65, 76, 'IP-Address'), (90, 126, 'Token keys')]"
"On 2023-12-01, user Dave logged in from IP 198.51.100.23 using token key ZXCVBNMASDFGHJKLQWERTYUIOP123456.","[(3, 13, 'DATE'), (19, 23, 'PER'), (43, 56, 'IP-Address'), (70, 106, 'Token keys')]"
Server 10.0.0.5 responded to request with token key QWERTY123456ASDFGH7890ZXCVBNMLKJH and reported error by admin Eve.,"[(7, 14, 'IP-Address'), (43, 79, 'Token keys'), (100, 103, 'PER')]"
The 4th update was installed on the router at IP 172.31.255.255 with token key 1A2B3C4D5E6F7G8H9I0J1K2L3M4N5O6P.,"[(4, 7, 'ORDINAL'), (47, 59, 'IP-Address'), (73, 109, 'Token keys')]"
"Translator Maria submitted the document 'The Art of NER' from IP 203.0.113.75, token key LMNOPQRSTUVWX123456789YZABCD5678.","[(11, 16, 'PER'), (34, 48, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (54, 65, 'IP-Address'), (77, 113, 'Token keys')]"
Payment of $2500 was received from organization TechCorp on IP 198.18.0.1 with transaction token key ZX12345CVBNM67890LKJHGFEDSAQWERTY.,"[(11, 15, 'MONEY'), (34, 42, 'ORG'), (46, 57, 'IP-Address'), (81, 121, 'Token keys')]"
The 2nd backup ran successfully at 2024-05-20 from IP 10.10.10.10 with token key ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ1234567890.,"[(4, 7, 'ORDINAL'), (34, 44, 'DATE'), (50, 60, 'IP-Address'), (74, 114, 'Token keys')]"
Tech lead Sarah accessed the system from IP 255.255.255.255 and presented the report 'Network Analysis' with token key 1Q2W3E4R5T6Y7U8I9O0P.,"[(10, 15, 'PER'), (46, 59, 'IP-Address'), (78, 95, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (109, 129, 'Token keys')]"
Server log shows connection from IPv6 address 2001:db8::ff00:42:8329 with token key A1B2C3D4E5F6G7H8I9J0K1L2M3N4O5P6 and user Mike.,"[(35, 53, 'IP-Address'), (69, 105, 'Token keys'), (110, 114, 'PER')]"
The software 'DeepScan v3.1' licensed to company Globex had an IP 192.168.100.100 and token key HGFEDCBA1234567890QWERTYUIOPLKJH.,"[(13, 26, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (44, 51, 'ORG'), (60, 73, 'IP-Address'), (87, 127, 'Token keys')]"
"On 2023-07-04, engineer John connected via IP 8.8.8.8 using token key ZXCV1234ASDF5678QWER9012TYUI3456 to deploy updates.","[(3, 13, 'DATE'), (22, 26, 'PER'), (39, 46, 'IP-Address'), (60, 96, 'Token keys')]"
The quarterly report Q2-2024 was submitted by Finance Dept from IP 192.0.2.1 with token key MNBVCXZLKJHGFDSAPOIUYTREWQ123456.,"[(22, 29, 'MISC'), (44, 59, 'ORG'), (65, 75, 'IP-Address'), (89, 129, 'Token keys')]"
Developer Emily fixed bug #4523 on server 172.20.10.5 and used token key 1234ABCD5678EFGH9012IJKL3456MNOP.,"[(10, 15, 'PER'), (36, 48, 'IP-Address'), (60, 96, 'Token keys')]"
The meeting scheduled on 2024-01-15 at HQ IP 10.1.1.1 will require tokens like ZYXWVUTSRQPONMLKJIHGFEDCBA9876543210.,"[(22, 32, 'DATE'), (36, 44, 'LOC'), (45, 52, 'IP-Address'), (76, 116, 'Token keys')]"
User Carlos accessed the database at IP 100.64.0.1 with token key A1S2D3F4G5H6J7K8L9Q0W1E2R3T4Y5U6.,"[(5, 11, 'PER'), (44, 54, 'IP-Address'), (68, 104, 'Token keys')]"
The new release 'Phoenix Update' was deployed on 127.0.0.1 with token key QWERTYUIOPASDFGHJKLZXCVBNM123456.,"[(16, 31, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (47, 58, 'IP-Address'), (72, 108, 'Token keys')]"
IT admin Laura reported a breach attempt from IP 203.0.113.195 and used token key 1QAZ2WSX3EDC4RFV5TGB6YHN7UJM8IK9OLP0.,"[(9, 14, 'PER'), (52, 65, 'IP-Address'), (79, 119, 'Token keys')]"
The server at 192.168.254.254 responded to ping with token key ZXCVBNMASDFGHJKLQWERTYUIOP1234567890 and operator Tim.,"[(14, 28, 'IP-Address'), (52, 92, 'Token keys'), (105, 108, 'PER')]"
"On 2023-11-11, technician Zoe reset the router 10.0.0.254 using token key QAZWSXEDCRFVTGBYHNUJMIKOLP123456.","[(3, 13, 'DATE'), (24, 27, 'PER'), (38, 48, 'IP-Address'), (62, 102, 'Token keys')]"
"The license key for product 'DataSecure' expired on 2022-12-31, IP 198.51.100.99, token key MNBVCXZLKJHGFDSAPOIUYTREWQ1234.","[(31, 41, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (59, 69, 'DATE'), (71, 83, 'IP-Address'), (95, 131, 'Token keys')]"
Customer Alex reported latency issue from IP 172.217.10.14 with token key 1Q2W3E4R5T6Y7U8I9O0P1A2S3D4F5G6.,"[(9, 13, 'PER'), (41, 54, 'IP-Address'), (68, 104, 'Token keys')]"
The 5th generation firewall blocked suspicious traffic from IP 203.0.113.1 using token key ZXCVBNMLKJHGFDSAPOIUYTREWQ0987654321.,"[(4, 7, 'ORDINAL'), (66, 77, 'IP-Address'), (91, 131, 'Token keys')]"
System update version 2.3.4 was applied at 2024-03-30 on server IP 10.10.10.20 with token key ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ9876543210.,"[(15, 20, 'MISC'), (34, 44, 'DATE'), (54, 64, 'IP-Address'), (78, 118, 'Token keys')]"
Administrator Mike accessed admin panel from IP 192.0.2.100 and authenticated with token key 1234567890QWERTYUIOPLKJHGFDSAZXCV.,"[(14, 18, 'PER'), (49, 60, 'IP-Address'), (78, 118, 'Token keys')]"
The document 'System Architecture' authored by Dr. Smith was reviewed on 2024-06-01 from IP 198.51.100.42 with token key LKJHGFDSAMNBVCXZQWERTYUIOP1234567890.,"[(13, 32, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (45, 53, 'PER'), (67, 77, 'DATE'), (83, 96, 'IP-Address'), (110, 150, 'Token keys')]"
User Jan accessed the service from IPv6 address fe80::1ff:fe23:4567:890a with token key POIUYTREWQLKJHGFDSAMNBVCXZ1234567890.,"[(5, 8, 'PER'), (38, 60, 'IP-Address'), (74, 114, 'Token keys')]"
Payments totaling $1500 were processed by Finance Team on IP 10.255.255.1 with token key QWERTYUIOPASDFGHJKLZXCVBNM9876543210.,"[(17, 22, 'MONEY'), (39, 52, 'ORG'), (56, 67, 'IP-Address'), (81, 121, 'Token keys')]"
Engineer Lucy deployed patch KB123456 to node 192.168.0.101 using token key MNBVCXZLKJHGFDSAPOIUYTREWQ1234567890 on 2024-02-14.,"[(9, 13, 'PER'), (23, 32, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (41, 54, 'IP-Address'), (68, 108, 'Token keys'), (112, 122, 'DATE')]"
"The 3rd server cluster at IP 172.16.0.5 failed health check, token key ASDFGHJKLQWERTYUIOPZXCVBNM1234567890 assigned for recovery.","[(4, 7, 'ORDINAL'), (25, 36, 'IP-Address'), (53, 93, 'Token keys')]"
System alert triggered by admin Olivia from IP 203.0.113.25 with token key ZXCVBNMASDFGHJKLQWERTYUIOP123456.,"[(23, 29, 'PER'), (43, 56, 'IP-Address'), (70, 110, 'Token keys')]"
The software 'CyberGuard' version 1.0 was installed on 192.168.10.10 with token key QAZWSXEDCRFVTGBYHNUJMIKOLP1234567.,"[(13, 23, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (44, 55, 'IP-Address'), (69, 109, 'Token keys')]"
User Liam from Berlin logged in via IPv6 2001:0db8:85a3:0000:0000:8a2e:0370:7334 using token key 1Q2W3E4R5T6Y7U8I9O0P1A2S3D4F5G6H.,"[(5, 9, 'PER'), (15, 21, 'LOC'), (35, 72, 'IP-Address'), (86, 126, 'Token keys')]"
"On 2024-05-05, the database server 10.20.30.40 received token key ZXCVBNMASDFGHJKLQWERTYUIOP12345678 from user Emma.","[(3, 13, 'DATE'), (29, 40, 'IP-Address'), (55, 95, 'Token keys'), (106, 110, 'PER')]"
Company NetSolutions updated firewall rules on 192.0.2.50 with token key MNBVCXZLKJHGFDSAPOIUYTREWQ9876543210 effective 2024-07-01.,"[(8, 21, 'ORG'), (44, 55, 'IP-Address'), (69, 109, 'Token keys'), (120, 130, 'DATE')]"
Technician Noah rebooted server 172.31.0.100 and used token key ASDFGHJKLQWERTYUIOPZXCVBNM123456 to restore services.,"[(11, 15, 'PER'), (33, 45, 'IP-Address'), (58, 98, 'Token keys')]"
"The 1st quarter earnings report was prepared by Finance Dept on IP 198.51.100.10, token key QWERTYUIOPASDFGHJKLZXCVBNM123456.","[(4, 7, 'ORDINAL'), (40, 55, 'ORG'), (61, 73, 'IP-Address'), (85, 125, 'Token keys')]"
User Ava accessed the VPN from IPv6 address fe80::a6db:30ff:fe98:e946 with token key ZXCVBNMLKJHGFDSAPOIUYTREWQ1234567890.,"[(5, 8, 'PER'), (30, 54, 'IP-Address'), (68, 108, 'Token keys')]"
Patch KB7891011 was installed on 10.10.20.30 with token key MNBVCXZLKJHGFDSAPOIUYTREWQ0987654321 by admin Ethan.,"[(6, 16, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (30, 41, 'IP-Address'), (55, 95, 'Token keys'), (104, 109, 'PER')]"
The server 192.168.1.200 rebooted at 2024-06-30 following token key 1234567890QWERTYUIOPLKJHGFDSAZXCV for authentication.,"[(11, 24, 'IP-Address'), (33, 43, 'DATE'), (54, 94, 'Token keys')]"
Network engineer Mia updated router configs on IP 203.0.113.10 using token key POIUYTREWQLKJHGFDSAMNBVCXZ123456.,"[(17, 20, 'PER'), (41, 54, 'IP-Address'), (68, 108, 'Token keys')]"
The new feature 'SecureConnect' was rolled out by DevTeam at IP 10.0.0.99 with token key QWERTYUIOPASDFGHJKLZXCVBNM9876543210.,"[(18, 31, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (48, 56, 'ORG'), (60, 70, 'IP-Address'), (84, 124, 'Token keys')]"
"On 2024-03-15, operator Jack logged in from IP 172.16.254.254 and authenticated with token key ZXCVBNMASDFGHJKLQWERTYUIOP123456.","[(3, 13, 'DATE'), (26, 30, 'PER'), (44, 57, 'IP-Address'), (71, 111, 'Token keys')]"
"Server load average exceeded threshold on 192.0.2.200, token key MNBVCXZLKJHGFDSAPOIUYTREWQ1234567890 used for diagnostics.","[(43, 56, 'IP-Address'), (70, 110, 'Token keys')]"
Jessica deployed patch KB1002003 to server 10.10.10.100 with token key ASDFGHJKLQWERTYUIOPZXCVBNM9876543210.,"[(0, 7, 'PER'), (26, 36, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (40, 52, 'IP-Address'), (66, 106, 'Token keys')]"
The translation team updated the manual 'QuickStart Guide' in English from IP 203.0.113.15 using token key ZXCVBNMASDFGHJKLQWERTYUIOP123456.,"[(4, 20, 'ORG'), (39, 55, 'WORK_OF_ART'), (59, 66, 'LANGUAGE'), (72, 85, 'IP-Address'), (99, 139, 'Token keys')]"
