,sentence,tokens,tags,Indicator
0,"During the conference in New York, the token h4jd93kslqw8EYTU12 was verified from IP 192.168.1.15.","['During', 'the', 'conference', 'in', 'New', 'York', ',', 'the', 'token', 'h4jd93kslqw8EYTU12', 'was', 'verified', 'from', 'IP', '192.168.1.15', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
1,Amazon hired a new employee with token ZXCVBNM123456qwerty and IP 2001:0db8:85a3:0000:0000:8a2e:0370:7334.,"['Amazon', 'hired', 'a', 'new', 'employee', 'with', 'token', 'ZXCVBNM123456qwerty', 'and', 'IP', '2001:0db8:85a3:0000:0000:8a2e:0370:7334', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
2,"On March 5th, Dr. Emily Clark accessed the system using token a1b2c3d4e5f6g7h8i9j0 and IP 10.0.0.254.","['On', 'March', '5th', ',', 'Dr.', 'Emily', 'Clark', 'accessed', 'the', 'system', 'using', 'token', 'a1b2c3d4e5f6g7h8i9j0', 'and', 'IP', '10.0.0.254', '.']","['O', 'B-tim', 'I-tim', 'O', 'B-per', 'I-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
3,Microsoft announced on January 12th that token QWERTYUIOPASDFGHJKL was compromised at IP 172.16.254.1.,"['Microsoft', 'announced', 'on', 'January', '12th', 'that', 'token', 'QWERTYUIOPASDFGHJKL', 'was', 'compromised', 'at', 'IP', '172.16.254.1', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'O', 'B-tim', 'I-tim', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
4,The summit held in Berlin featured token ZX12345ABCD67890EFGH and IP address 8.8.8.8.,"['The', 'summit', 'held', 'in', 'Berlin', 'featured', 'token', 'ZX12345ABCD67890EFGH', 'and', 'IP', 'address', '8.8.8.8', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
5,President John Doe logged in using token TYU89JKL34MNOPQ12 and IP 123.45.67.89 during the summit in Washington.,"['President', 'John', 'Doe', 'logged', 'in', 'using', 'token', 'TYU89JKL34MNOPQ12', 'and', 'IP', '123.45.67.89', 'during', 'the', 'summit', 'in', 'Washington', '.']","['O', 'B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O']",True
6,"On 2023-04-01, Google reported a breach involving token LKMN89VBGH12345ZXCV and IP 2400:cb00:2048:1::c629:d7a2.","['On', '2023-04-01', ',', 'Google', 'reported', 'a', 'breach', 'involving', 'token', 'LKMN89VBGH12345ZXCV', 'and', 'IP', '2400:cb00:2048:1::c629:d7a2', '.']","['O', 'B-tim', 'O', 'B-org', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
7,The festival in Rio de Janeiro used token QAZWSXEDCRFVTGBYHNUJ and IP 255.255.255.0 for access control.,"['The', 'festival', 'in', 'Rio', 'de', 'Janeiro', 'used', 'token', 'QAZWSXEDCRFVTGBYHNUJ', 'and', 'IP', '255.255.255.0', 'for', 'access', 'control', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'I-geo', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']",True
8,Tesla's CEO Elon Musk verified token PLMOKNIJBUHGVFDSAQW12345 with IP 192.0.2.146 yesterday.,"['Tesla', ""'s"", 'CEO', 'Elon', 'Musk', 'verified', 'token', 'PLMOKNIJBUHGVFDSAQW12345', 'with', 'IP', '192.0.2.146', 'yesterday', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'O', 'B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'B-tim', 'O']",True
9,"On July 20th, the University of Oxford issued token ZXCVBNMLKJHGFDSA12 and logged IP 172.217.10.14.","['On', 'July', '20th', ',', 'the', 'University', 'of', 'Oxford', 'issued', 'token', 'ZXCVBNMLKJHGFDSA12', 'and', 'logged', 'IP', '172.217.10.14', '.']","['O', 'B-tim', 'I-tim', 'O', 'O', 'B-org', 'I-org', 'I-org', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
10,Facebook reported that token 9Q8W7E6R5T4Y3U2I1OP was stolen from IP 2607:f8b0:4005:805::200e.,"['Facebook', 'reported', 'that', 'token', '9Q8W7E6R5T4Y3U2I1OP', 'was', 'stolen', 'from', 'IP', '2607:f8b0:4005:805::200e', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
11,The meeting in San Francisco on 09/15/2023 used token ZXCV1234ASDF5678QWER and IP 198.51.100.23.,"['The', 'meeting', 'in', 'San', 'Francisco', 'on', '09/15/2023', 'used', 'token', 'ZXCV1234ASDF5678QWER', 'and', 'IP', '198.51.100.23', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
12,IBM's new server token QW12ER34TY56UI78OP90 is accessible via IP 172.31.255.255.,"['IBM', ""'s"", 'new', 'server', 'token', 'QW12ER34TY56UI78OP90', 'is', 'accessible', 'via', 'IP', '172.31.255.255', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
13,Angela Merkel accessed the portal with token QAZXSWEDCVFRTGBNHYUJ and IP fd12:3456:789a:1::1.,"['Angela', 'Merkel', 'accessed', 'the', 'portal', 'with', 'token', 'QAZXSWEDCVFRTGBNHYUJ', 'and', 'IP', 'fd12:3456:789a:1::1', '.']","['B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
14,The event in Tokyo featured keynote speaker token MNBVXZLKJHGFDSA987 and IP 203.0.113.76.,"['The', 'event', 'in', 'Tokyo', 'featured', 'keynote', 'speaker', 'token', 'MNBVXZLKJHGFDSA987', 'and', 'IP', '203.0.113.76', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
15,IBM and Google collaborated on token ASDFGHJKLQWERTYUIOP123 and IP 192.0.2.33 last week.,"['IBM', 'and', 'Google', 'collaborated', 'on', 'token', 'ASDFGHJKLQWERTYUIOP123', 'and', 'IP', '192.0.2.33', 'last', 'week', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'B-org', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'B-tim', 'I-tim', 'O']",True
16,"On October 10, 2022, token ZXCVBNMASDFGHJKL987 was linked to IP 172.20.10.5 at Microsoft HQ.","['On', 'October', '10', ',', '2022', ',', 'token', 'ZXCVBNMASDFGHJKL987', 'was', 'linked', 'to', 'IP', '172.20.10.5', 'at', 'Microsoft', 'HQ', '.']","['O', 'B-tim', 'I-tim', 'O', 'I-tim', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'B-org', 'O', 'O']",True
17,"The CEO of Apple, Tim Cook, used token QWER1234TYUI5678ASDF and IP 198.162.0.1 yesterday.","['The', 'CEO', 'of', 'Apple', ',', 'Tim', 'Cook', ',', 'used', 'token', 'QWER1234TYUI5678ASDF', 'and', 'IP', '198.162.0.1', 'yesterday', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-org', 'O', 'B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'B-tim', 'O']",True
18,The conference in London started at 9 AM with token ZXCVBNMLKJHGFDSA09 and IP 203.0.113.12.,"['The', 'conference', 'in', 'London', 'started', 'at', '9', 'AM', 'with', 'token', 'ZXCVBNMLKJHGFDSA09', 'and', 'IP', '203.0.113.12', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'B-tim', 'I-tim', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
19,Dr. Sarah Johnson from Harvard University used token ASDF1234ZXCV5678QWER and IP 10.10.10.10.,"['Dr.', 'Sarah', 'Johnson', 'from', 'Harvard', 'University', 'used', 'token', 'ASDF1234ZXCV5678QWER', 'and', 'IP', '10.10.10.10', '.']","['O', 'B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'B-org', 'I-org', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
20,"On December 31st, token QWERTY123456ASDFGHJKL was accessed via IP 172.16.0.254 in Los Angeles.","['On', 'December', '31st', ',', 'token', 'QWERTY123456ASDFGHJKL', 'was', 'accessed', 'via', 'IP', '172.16.0.254', 'in', 'Los', 'Angeles', '.']","['O', 'B-tim', 'I-tim', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'O']",True
21,Elon Musk tweeted about token ZXCVBNMLKJHGFDSAQWER and IP 2400:cb00:2048:1::c629:d7a2 yesterday.,"['Elon', 'Musk', 'tweeted', 'about', 'token', 'ZXCVBNMLKJHGFDSAQWER', 'and', 'IP', '2400:cb00:2048:1::c629:d7a2', 'yesterday', '.']","['B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'B-tim', 'O']",True
22,The Berlin office logged token QAZXSWEDCVFRTGBNHYUJ and IP 198.51.100.45 at noon.,"['The', 'Berlin', 'office', 'logged', 'token', 'QAZXSWEDCVFRTGBNHYUJ', 'and', 'IP', '198.51.100.45', 'at', 'noon', '.']","['O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O']",True
23,Apple's token ZXCVBNMASDFGHJKL123 was compromised from IP 10.0.0.1 last Friday.,"['Apple', ""'s"", 'token', 'ZXCVBNMASDFGHJKL123', 'was', 'compromised', 'from', 'IP', '10.0.0.1', 'last', 'Friday', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O']",True
24,"In Paris, token ASDFGHJKLZXCVBNMQWERT was used to access IP 203.0.113.1 during the gala.","['In', 'Paris', ',', 'token', 'ASDFGHJKLZXCVBNMQWERT', 'was', 'used', 'to', 'access', 'IP', '203.0.113.1', 'during', 'the', 'gala', '.']","['O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']",True
25,Mark Zuckerberg accessed the Facebook system with token QWERTYUIOPASDFGHJKL and IP 192.168.100.100.,"['Mark', 'Zuckerberg', 'accessed', 'the', 'Facebook', 'system', 'with', 'token', 'QWERTYUIOPASDFGHJKL', 'and', 'IP', '192.168.100.100', '.']","['B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'B-org', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
26,The summit in Dubai began at 14:00 with token ZXCVBNMASDFGHJKL098 and IP 203.0.113.9.,"['The', 'summit', 'in', 'Dubai', 'began', 'at', '14:00', 'with', 'token', 'ZXCVBNMASDFGHJKL098', 'and', 'IP', '203.0.113.9', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
27,Dr. Jane Smith from MIT used token QAZWSXEDCRFVTGBYHNUJ and IP 172.16.254.1.,"['Dr.', 'Jane', 'Smith', 'from', 'MIT', 'used', 'token', 'QAZWSXEDCRFVTGBYHNUJ', 'and', 'IP', '172.16.254.1', '.']","['O', 'B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'B-org', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
28,The New York office generated token ZXCVBNMLKJHGFDSA123 and connected from IP 10.0.1.1.,"['The', 'New', 'York', 'office', 'generated', 'token', 'ZXCVBNMLKJHGFDSA123', 'and', 'connected', 'from', 'IP', '10.0.1.1', '.']","['O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
29,Google's headquarters in Mountain View issued token QWERTYUIOPLKJHGFDSAZX and IP 172.217.3.110.,"['Google', ""'s"", 'headquarters', 'in', 'Mountain', 'View', 'issued', 'token', 'QWERTYUIOPLKJHGFDSAZX', 'and', 'IP', '172.217.3.110', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
30,"On February 28, token ASDFGHJKLZXCVBNMQWERTY was logged from IP 198.51.100.7 in Madrid.","['On', 'February', '28', ',', 'token', 'ASDFGHJKLZXCVBNMQWERTY', 'was', 'logged', 'from', 'IP', '198.51.100.7', 'in', 'Madrid', '.']","['O', 'B-tim', 'I-tim', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O']",True
31,Microsoft employee token ZXCVBNMASDFGHJKL12345 accessed IP 10.1.1.1 on Monday.,"['Microsoft', 'employee', 'token', 'ZXCVBNMASDFGHJKL12345', 'accessed', 'IP', '10.1.1.1', 'on', 'Monday', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O']",True
32,The workshop in Seattle started with token QWERTYUIOPLKJHGFDSAZ and IP 192.0.2.55.,"['The', 'workshop', 'in', 'Seattle', 'started', 'with', 'token', 'QWERTYUIOPLKJHGFDSAZ', 'and', 'IP', '192.0.2.55', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
33,Elon Musk's token ZXCVBNMASDFGHJKL098 was accessed from IP 2404:6800:4003:c01::64 yesterday.,"['Elon', 'Musk', ""'s"", 'token', 'ZXCVBNMASDFGHJKL098', 'was', 'accessed', 'from', 'IP', '2404:6800:4003:c01::64', 'yesterday', '.']","['B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'B-tim', 'O']",True
34,"During the gala in Rome, token ASDFGHJKLZXCVBNMQWERTY was validated with IP 203.0.113.21.","['During', 'the', 'gala', 'in', 'Rome', ',', 'token', 'ASDFGHJKLZXCVBNMQWERTY', 'was', 'validated', 'with', 'IP', '203.0.113.21', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
35,Harvard University's token ZXCVBNMLKJHGFDSA123 was used from IP 172.217.5.110 last month.,"['Harvard', 'University', ""'s"", 'token', 'ZXCVBNMLKJHGFDSA123', 'was', 'used', 'from', 'IP', '172.217.5.110', 'last', 'month', '.']","['B-org', 'I-org', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O']",True
36,The token QWERTYUIOPASDFGHJKL was issued by Google from IP 192.168.50.50 during the event.,"['The', 'token', 'QWERTYUIOPASDFGHJKL', 'was', 'issued', 'by', 'Google', 'from', 'IP', '192.168.50.50', 'during', 'the', 'event', '.']","['O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-org', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']",True
37,Angela Merkel's token ZXCVBNMASDFGHJKL was logged from IP 10.10.10.10 on Tuesday.,"['Angela', 'Merkel', ""'s"", 'token', 'ZXCVBNMASDFGHJKL', 'was', 'logged', 'from', 'IP', '10.10.10.10', 'on', 'Tuesday', '.']","['B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O']",True
38,Facebook's token QWERTYUIOPLKJHGFDSAZ was accessed via IP 203.0.113.15 yesterday.,"['Facebook', ""'s"", 'token', 'QWERTYUIOPLKJHGFDSAZ', 'was', 'accessed', 'via', 'IP', '203.0.113.15', 'yesterday', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'B-tim', 'O']",True
39,The Seattle office issued token ZXCVBNMLKJHGFDSA and logged IP 192.0.2.100 last week.,"['The', 'Seattle', 'office', 'issued', 'token', 'ZXCVBNMLKJHGFDSA', 'and', 'logged', 'IP', '192.0.2.100', 'last', 'week', '.']","['O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'B-tim', 'I-tim', 'O']",True
40,IBM's token QAZWSXEDCRFVTGBY was compromised from IP 172.31.255.255 yesterday.,"['IBM', ""'s"", 'token', 'QAZWSXEDCRFVTGBY', 'was', 'compromised', 'from', 'IP', '172.31.255.255', 'yesterday', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'B-tim', 'O']",True
41,The token ZXCVBNMASDFGHJKL987 was used in the London office with IP 198.51.100.99.,"['The', 'token', 'ZXCVBNMASDFGHJKL987', 'was', 'used', 'in', 'the', 'London', 'office', 'with', 'IP', '198.51.100.99', '.']","['O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
42,Tim Cook accessed the system using token QWERTYUIOPASDFGHJKL and IP 192.168.0.1.,"['Tim', 'Cook', 'accessed', 'the', 'system', 'using', 'token', 'QWERTYUIOPASDFGHJKL', 'and', 'IP', '192.168.0.1', '.']","['B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
43,"On March 3rd, token ZXCVBNMLKJHGFDSA123 was accessed from IP 10.10.10.10 in Chicago.","['On', 'March', '3rd', ',', 'token', 'ZXCVBNMLKJHGFDSA123', 'was', 'accessed', 'from', 'IP', '10.10.10.10', 'in', 'Chicago', '.']","['O', 'B-tim', 'I-tim', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O']",True
44,Google's token ASDFGHJKLZXCVBNMQWERTY was compromised from IP 172.217.3.110 yesterday.,"['Google', ""'s"", 'token', 'ASDFGHJKLZXCVBNMQWERTY', 'was', 'compromised', 'from', 'IP', '172.217.3.110', 'yesterday', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'B-tim', 'O']",True
45,"At 8 PM, the token ZXCVBNMLKJHGFDSA was used from IP 192.168.1.100 in Berlin.","['At', '8', 'PM', ',', 'the', 'token', 'ZXCVBNMLKJHGFDSA', 'was', 'used', 'from', 'IP', '192.168.1.100', 'in', 'Berlin', '.']","['O', 'B-tim', 'I-tim', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O']",True
46,Elon Musk's token QWERTYUIOPASDFGHJKL was accessed via IP 10.0.0.2 yesterday.,"['Elon', 'Musk', ""'s"", 'token', 'QWERTYUIOPASDFGHJKL', 'was', 'accessed', 'via', 'IP', '10.0.0.2', 'yesterday', '.']","['B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'B-tim', 'O']",True
47,The festival in Rio used token ZXCVBNMLKJHGFDSA and IP 203.0.113.10 for authentication.,"['The', 'festival', 'in', 'Rio', 'used', 'token', 'ZXCVBNMLKJHGFDSA', 'and', 'IP', '203.0.113.10', 'for', 'authentication', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O']",True
48,Microsoft's token ASDFGHJKLZXCVBNMQWERT was compromised from IP 172.16.0.1 last week.,"['Microsoft', ""'s"", 'token', 'ASDFGHJKLZXCVBNMQWERT', 'was', 'compromised', 'from', 'IP', '172.16.0.1', 'last', 'week', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O']",True
49,The token QWERTYUIOPASDFGHJKL was issued by Facebook from IP 192.168.1.1 during the event.,"['The', 'token', 'QWERTYUIOPASDFGHJKL', 'was', 'issued', 'by', 'Facebook', 'from', 'IP', '192.168.1.1', 'during', 'the', 'event', '.']","['O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-org', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']",True
50,Angela Merkel's token ZXCVBNMASDFGHJKL was logged from IP 10.10.10.10 on Wednesday.,"['Angela', 'Merkel', ""'s"", 'token', 'ZXCVBNMASDFGHJKL', 'was', 'logged', 'from', 'IP', '10.10.10.10', 'on', 'Wednesday', '.']","['B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O']",True
51,Facebook's token QWERTYUIOPLKJHGFDSAZ was accessed via IP 203.0.113.15 yesterday.,"['Facebook', ""'s"", 'token', 'QWERTYUIOPLKJHGFDSAZ', 'was', 'accessed', 'via', 'IP', '203.0.113.15', 'yesterday', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'B-tim', 'O']",True
52,The Seattle office issued token ZXCVBNMLKJHGFDSA and logged IP 192.0.2.100 last Friday.,"['The', 'Seattle', 'office', 'issued', 'token', 'ZXCVBNMLKJHGFDSA', 'and', 'logged', 'IP', '192.0.2.100', 'last', 'Friday', '.']","['O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O']",True
0,Dr. Alexandra Vostrikov accessed the server 2a03:2880:f10d:83:face:b00c::25de yesterday in Berlin.,"['Dr.', 'Alexandra', 'Vostrikov', 'accessed', 'the', 'server', '9js82kdhf7wqle2k3jf4h', '2a03:2880:f10d:83:face:b00c::25de', 'yesterday', 'in', 'Berlin', '.']","['B-per', 'I-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'U-IP', 'B-tim', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O']",True
1,The IP address 192.168.178.45 was assigned to user ID kx9ruw82jdh3mfoq at Google headquarters in Mountain View.,"['The', 'IP', 'address', '192.168.178.45', 'was', 'assigned', 'to', 'user', 'ID', 'kx9ruw82jdh3mfoq', 'at', 'Google', 'headquarters', 'in', 'Mountain', 'View', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'B-org', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'O']",True
2,"On 2023-11-15, the analyst s8d9fh237dsjklx reported a breach from IP fe80::1ff:fe23:4567:890a at the United Nations.","['On', '2023-11-15', ',', 'the', 'analyst', 's8d9fh237dsjklx', 'reported', 'a', 'breach', 'from', 'IP', 'fe80::1ff:fe23:4567:890a', 'at', 'the', 'United', 'Nations', '.']","['O', 'B-tim', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'B-org', 'I-org', 'O']",True
3,Maria-Jose Carvajal's temporary authorization token v9x2klj3h4f8wq was used from 10.0.0.255 during the event in Madrid.,"['Maria-Jose', ""Carvajal's"", 'temporary', 'authorization', 'token', 'v9x2klj3h4f8wq', 'was', 'used', 'from', '10.0.0.255', 'during', 'the', 'event', 'in', 'Madrid', '.']","['B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O']",True
4,"Yesterday, engineer qwe87rtyuio123plm from NASA accessed 172.31.255.254 for system diagnostics.","['Yesterday', ',', 'engineer', 'qwe87rtyuio123plm', 'from', 'NASA', 'accessed', '172.31.255.254', 'for', 'system', 'diagnostics', '.']","['B-tim', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'B-org', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']",True
5,The software update was pushed on 2024-01-30 by admin user zxcnm123lkjhgfds from the IP 2001:0db8:85a3:0000:0000:8a2e:0370:7334.,"['The', 'software', 'update', 'was', 'pushed', 'on', '2024-01-30', 'by', 'admin', 'user', 'zxcnm123lkjhgfds', 'from', 'the', 'IP', '2001:0db8:85a3:0000:0000:8a2e:0370:7334', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
6,The conference in New York City featured a keynote by Dr. Stefan Lorenz with token k9l8j7h6g5f4e3d2c1b0 and IP 198.51.100.23.,"['The', 'conference', 'in', 'New', 'York', 'City', 'featured', 'a', 'keynote', 'by', 'Dr.', 'Stefan', 'Lorenz', 'with', 'token', 'k9l8j7h6g5f4e3d2c1b0', 'and', 'IP', '198.51.100.23', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'I-geo', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-per', 'I-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
8,Agent Mark Thompson's access token 8h7g6f5d4s3a2q1w0e9r was traced back to IPv6 address 2607:f0d0:1002:51::4.,"['Agent', 'Mark', ""Thompson's"", 'access', 'token', '8h7g6f5d4s3a2q1w0e9r', 'was', 'traced', 'back', 'to', 'IPv6', 'address', '2607:f0d0:1002:51::4', '.']","['O', 'B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
9,"The CEO of TechSphere, Anna Müller, logged in from IP 172.217.12.14 using token q1w2e3r4t5y6u7i8o9p0.","['The', 'CEO', 'of', 'TechSphere', ',', 'Anna', 'Müller', ',', 'logged', 'in', 'from', 'IP', '172.217.12.14', 'using', 'token', 'q1w2e3r4t5y6u7i8o9p0', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-org', 'O', 'B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
10,"During the summit held on 2024-05-10 in Paris, token a1b2c3d4e5f6g7h8i9j0 was distributed to all participants, IP 10.10.10.10.","['During', 'the', 'summit', 'held', 'on', '2024-05-10', 'in', 'Paris', ',', 'token', 'a1b2c3d4e5f6g7h8i9j0', 'was', 'distributed', 'to', 'all', 'participants', ',', 'IP', '10.10.10.10', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
11,Professor Liu Wei in Beijing received token zxcasdqwe1234567890 and accessed IP 192.0.2.146 during the conference.,"['Professor', 'Liu', 'Wei', 'in', 'Beijing', 'received', 'token', 'zxcasdqwe1234567890', 'and', 'accessed', 'IP', '192.0.2.146', 'during', 'the', 'conference', '.']","['O', 'B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']",True
12,The startup InnoTech deployed new credentials for user token hjklpoiuy0987654321 and IP 172.20.14.2 last week.,"['The', 'startup', 'InnoTech', 'deployed', 'new', 'credentials', 'for', 'user', 'token', 'hjklpoiuy0987654321', 'and', 'IP', '172.20.14.2', 'last', 'week', '.']","['O', 'O', 'B-org', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'B-tim', 'I-tim', 'O']",True
13,"On March 3rd, 2024, Dr. Samuel Green logged in from IPv6 address 2001:0db8:85a3::8a2e:0370:7334 with token lkjasdf987qwertyuio.","['On', 'March', '3rd', ',', '2024', ',', 'Dr.', 'Samuel', 'Green', 'logged', 'in', 'from', 'IPv6', 'address', '2001:0db8:85a3::8a2e:0370:7334', 'with', 'token', 'lkjasdf987qwertyuio', '.']","['O', 'B-tim', 'I-tim', 'O', 'I-tim', 'O', 'B-per', 'I-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
14,The multinational company Globex Corp issued token mnbvcxzlkjhgfdsapoiuy and tracked IP 203.0.113.77 during the audit.,"['The', 'multinational', 'company', 'Globex', 'Corp', 'issued', 'token', 'mnbvcxzlkjhgfdsapoiuy', 'and', 'tracked', 'IP', '203.0.113.77', 'during', 'the', 'audit', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-org', 'I-org', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']",True
15,"Last Friday, hacker token 123abc456def789ghi was traced to IP 198.51.100.99 near San Francisco.","['Last', 'Friday', ',', 'hacker', 'token', '123abc456def789ghi', 'was', 'traced', 'to', 'IP', '198.51.100.99', 'near', 'San', 'Francisco', '.']","['O', 'B-tim', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'O']",True
16,The cybersecurity seminar in Tokyo featured expert token 7g6h5j4k3l2m1n0b9v8c and IP fe80::200:f8ff:fe21:67cf.,"['The', 'cybersecurity', 'seminar', 'in', 'Tokyo', 'featured', 'expert', 'token', '7g6h5j4k3l2m1n0b9v8c', 'and', 'IP', 'fe80::200:f8ff:fe21:67cf', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
17,"During the meeting on 2023-12-12, CEO John Matthews used token zxcvbnmasdfghjklqwer and IP 192.168.0.1.","['During', 'the', 'meeting', 'on', '2023-12-12', ',', 'CEO', 'John', 'Matthews', 'used', 'token', 'zxcvbnmasdfghjklqwer', 'and', 'IP', '192.168.0.1', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O', 'O', 'B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
18,The developer token qwertyuiopasdfghjkl was linked to IP 203.0.113.85 during the hackathon hosted in Amsterdam.,"['The', 'developer', 'token', 'qwertyuiopasdfghjkl', 'was', 'linked', 'to', 'IP', '203.0.113.85', 'during', 'the', 'hackathon', 'hosted', 'in', 'Amsterdam', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O']",True
19,"At 08:30 AM, security officer token asdf1234lkjh5678qwer accessed IPv6 address fd12:3456:789a:1::1 in London.","['At', '08:30', 'AM', ',', 'security', 'officer', 'token', 'asdf1234lkjh5678qwer', 'accessed', 'IPv6', 'address', 'fd12:3456:789a:1::1', 'in', 'London', '.']","['O', 'B-tim', 'I-tim', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O']",True
20,"Yesterday evening, the engineer k1l2m3n4o5p6q7r8s9t0 connected from IP 192.0.2.255 to the headquarters in Toronto.","['Yesterday', 'evening', ',', 'the', 'engineer', 'k1l2m3n4o5p6q7r8s9t0', 'connected', 'from', 'IP', '192.0.2.255', 'to', 'the', 'headquarters', 'in', 'Toronto', '.']","['B-tim', 'I-tim', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O']",True
0,Dr. Emily Johnson from Stanford University accessed the server at 192.168.1.101 yesterday.,"['Dr.', 'Emily', 'Johnson', 'from', 'Stanford', 'University', 'accessed', 'the', 'server', 'at', '192.168.1.101', 'yesterday', '.']","['B-per', 'I-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'B-org', 'I-org', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'B-tim', 'O']",True
1,"In New York City, the token KJH762hsdf98YUIOPQ was generated on 2023-05-12.","['In', 'New', 'York', 'City', ',', 'the', 'token', 'KJH762hsdf98YUIOPQ', 'was', 'generated', 'on', '2023-05-12', '.']","['O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'I-geo', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O']",True
2,Microsoft Corporation announced a new partnership in Seattle on 10th October 2022.,"['Microsoft', 'Corporation', 'announced', 'a', 'new', 'partnership', 'in', 'Seattle', 'on', '10th', 'October', '2022', '.']","['B-org', 'I-org', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'B-tim', 'I-tim', 'I-tim', 'O']",True
3,The user with token X8Y7Z6A5B4C3D2E1F0 connected from 2001:0db8:85a3:0000:0000:8a2e:0370:7334.,"['The', 'user', 'with', 'token', 'X8Y7Z6A5B4C3D2E1F0', 'connected', 'from', '2001:0db8:85a3:0000:0000:8a2e:0370:7334', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
4,Angela Merkel visited Berlin last Monday while carrying token ZXC12VBN98MLKJHGF.,"['Angela', 'Merkel', 'visited', 'Berlin', 'last', 'Monday', 'while', 'carrying', 'token', 'ZXC12VBN98MLKJHGF', '.']","['B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
5,The IP 10.0.0.254 was flagged during the attack on the headquarters of Tesla Inc. in Palo Alto.,"['The', 'IP', '10.0.0.254', 'was', 'flagged', 'during', 'the', 'attack', 'on', 'the', 'headquarters', 'of', 'Tesla', 'Inc.', 'in', 'Palo', 'Alto', '.']","['O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-org', 'I-org', 'O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'O']",True
6,"During the conference in Paris, token GHJK90IUYTREWQASD was distributed at 14:30 UTC.","['During', 'the', 'conference', 'in', 'Paris', ',', 'token', 'GHJK90IUYTREWQASD', 'was', 'distributed', 'at', '14:30', 'UTC', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-tim', 'I-tim', 'O']",True
7,IBM's new data center located in Austin uses the IP address 172.16.254.1.,"[""IBM's"", 'new', 'data', 'center', 'located', 'in', 'Austin', 'uses', 'the', 'IP', 'address', '172.16.254.1', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
8,"On 31st December 2023, token QWERTYUIOPLKJHGFDS was activated in London.","['On', '31st', 'December', '2023', ',', 'token', 'QWERTYUIOPLKJHGFDS', 'was', 'activated', 'in', 'London', '.']","['O', 'B-tim', 'I-tim', 'I-tim', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O']",True
9,Elon Musk tweeted from the IP 2607:f8b0:4005:805::200e during the Mars mission briefing.,"['Elon', 'Musk', 'tweeted', 'from', 'the', 'IP', '2607:f8b0:4005:805::200e', 'during', 'the', 'Mars', 'mission', 'briefing', '.']","['B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']",True
10,The token ZXCVBNMASDFGHJKLQWERTY was logged at 08:00 AM in Tokyo.,"['The', 'token', 'ZXCVBNMASDFGHJKLQWERTY', 'was', 'logged', 'at', '08:00', 'AM', 'in', 'Tokyo', '.']","['O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-tim', 'I-tim', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O']",True
11,Facebook's server with IP 54.239.28.85 is located in Menlo Park.,"[""Facebook's"", 'server', 'with', 'IP', '54.239.28.85', 'is', 'located', 'in', 'Menlo', 'Park', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'O']",True
12,The token HJG76YTR54EDCVBNML was compromised on 2024-01-15 in Washington D.C.,"['The', 'token', 'HJG76YTR54EDCVBNML', 'was', 'compromised', 'on', '2024-01-15', 'in', 'Washington', 'D.C.', '.']","['O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'O']",True
13,Prime Minister Boris Johnson logged in from the IP 203.0.113.5 during the summit.,"['Prime', 'Minister', 'Boris', 'Johnson', 'logged', 'in', 'from', 'the', 'IP', '203.0.113.5', 'during', 'the', 'summit', '.']","['B-per', 'I-per', 'I-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']",True
14,The encrypted token PLMOKNIJBUHVYGTFRD was issued in Berlin on 2022-11-23.,"['The', 'encrypted', 'token', 'PLMOKNIJBUHVYGTFRD', 'was', 'issued', 'in', 'Berlin', 'on', '2022-11-23', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O']",True
15,Google's data center at 2600:1901:0:18::f03c:91ff:feae:ed61 was attacked late last night.,"[""Google's"", 'data', 'center', 'at', '2600:1901:0:18::f03c:91ff:feae:ed61', 'was', 'attacked', 'late', 'last', 'night', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-tim', 'I-tim', 'O']",True
16,The token MNOPQRSTUVWX123456 was shared during the meeting in Chicago.,"['The', 'token', 'MNOPQRSTUVWX123456', 'was', 'shared', 'during', 'the', 'meeting', 'in', 'Chicago', '.']","['O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O']",True
17,Tesla's CEO Elon Musk accessed the system via 198.51.100.23 on Monday.,"[""Tesla's"", 'CEO', 'Elon', 'Musk', 'accessed', 'the', 'system', 'via', '198.51.100.23', 'on', 'Monday', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O']",True
18,The token ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOP was registered in Paris during the 2023 fashion week.,"['The', 'token', 'ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOP', 'was', 'registered', 'in', 'Paris', 'during', 'the', '2023', 'fashion', 'week', '.']","['O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O', 'O', 'O']",True
19,Admin token ZXCVBNMLKJHGFDSAQWERTY was used from 172.217.6.46 during the event.,"['Admin', 'token', 'ZXCVBNMLKJHGFDSAQWERTY', 'was', 'used', 'from', '172.217.6.46', 'during', 'the', 'event', '.']","['O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']",True
20,Prime Minister Narendra Modi's token LKAJSHD8723HKJ was compromised in New Delhi on 2022-09-01.,"['Prime', 'Minister', 'Narendra', ""Modi's"", 'token', 'LKAJSHD8723HKJ', 'was', 'compromised', 'in', 'New', 'Delhi', 'on', '2022-09-01', '.']","['B-per', 'I-per', 'I-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O']",True
0,"Yesterday, Dr. Emily Clarkson from Stanford University accessed the server at 192.168.1.1 using token xk39dkfjsl29dke12lqw.","['Yesterday', ',', 'Dr.', 'Emily', 'Clarkson', 'from', 'Stanford', 'University', 'accessed', 'the', 'server', 'at', '192.168.1.1', 'using', 'token', 'xk39dkfjsl29dke12lqw', '.']","['B-tim', 'O', 'O', 'B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'B-org', 'I-org', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
1,"In 2022, the Paris office of Acme Corp. received a login from 2001:0db8:85a3::8a2e:0370:7334 with token zxcvbnm1234567qwerty.","['In', '2022', ',', 'the', 'Paris', 'office', 'of', 'Acme', 'Corp.', 'received', 'a', 'login', 'from', '2001:0db8:85a3::8a2e:0370:7334', 'with', 'token', 'zxcvbnm1234567qwerty', '.']","['O', 'B-tim', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'B-org', 'I-org', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
2,Michael Jordan logged into the New York server at fe80::1ff:fe23:4567:890a using token qwertyuiop0987lkjhgfd.,"['Michael', 'Jordan', 'logged', 'into', 'the', 'New', 'York', 'server', 'at', 'fe80::1ff:fe23:4567:890a', 'using', 'token', 'qwertyuiop0987lkjhgfd', '.']","['B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
3,"On Monday, Google LLC in Mountain View assigned IP 10.0.0.254 to token asdfghjklqwertyuiop1234.","['On', 'Monday', ',', 'Google', 'LLC', 'in', 'Mountain', 'View', 'assigned', 'IP', '10.0.0.254', 'to', 'token', 'asdfghjklqwertyuiop1234', '.']","['O', 'B-tim', 'O', 'B-org', 'I-org', 'O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
4,Angela Merkel visited Berlin and then connected to 172.16.254.3 with token poiuytrewqlkjhgfdsamnbvc.,"['Angela', 'Merkel', 'visited', 'Berlin', 'and', 'then', 'connected', 'to', '172.16.254.3', 'with', 'token', 'poiuytrewqlkjhgfdsamnbvc', '.']","['B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
5,"At noon, IBM's London branch reported an access from 2607:f0d0:1002:51::4 using token mnbvcxzlkjhgfdsapoiuytrewq.","['At', 'noon', ',', 'IBM', ""'s"", 'London', 'branch', 'reported', 'an', 'access', 'from', '2607:f0d0:1002:51::4', 'using', 'token', 'mnbvcxzlkjhgfdsapoiuytrewq', '.']","['O', 'B-tim', 'O', 'B-org', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
6,President Joe Biden called from the White House via IP 192.0.2.146 while using token lkjhgfdsaqwertyuiopzxcvbnm.,"['President', 'Joe', 'Biden', 'called', 'from', 'the', 'White', 'House', 'via', 'IP', '192.0.2.146', 'while', 'using', 'token', 'lkjhgfdsaqwertyuiopzxcvbnm', '.']","['O', 'B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-org', 'I-org', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
7,Tesla's CEO Elon Musk tweeted from 198.51.100.23 using token qazwsxedcrfvtgbyhnujmikolp.,"['Tesla', ""'s"", 'CEO', 'Elon', 'Musk', 'tweeted', 'from', '198.51.100.23', 'using', 'token', 'qazwsxedcrfvtgbyhnujmikolp', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'O', 'B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
8,"During the summer of 2021, Facebook Inc. in Menlo Park logged in from 172.217.11.14 with token mkoijnuhbygvtfcrdxeszwaqpl.","['During', 'the', 'summer', 'of', '2021', ',', 'Facebook', 'Inc.', 'in', 'Menlo', 'Park', 'logged', 'in', 'from', '172.217.11.14', 'with', 'token', 'mkoijnuhbygvtfcrdxeszwaqpl', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O', 'B-org', 'I-org', 'O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
9,Dr. Sarah Connor checked into the Paris office on 15th July 2023 from IP fe80::200:f8ff:fe21:67cf with token poiuytrewqlkjhgfdsamnbvcxz.,"['Dr.', 'Sarah', 'Connor', 'checked', 'into', 'the', 'Paris', 'office', 'on', '15th', 'July', '2023', 'from', 'IP', 'fe80::200:f8ff:fe21:67cf', 'with', 'token', 'poiuytrewqlkjhgfdsamnbvcxz', '.']","['O', 'B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'B-tim', 'I-tim', 'I-tim', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
10,Amazon's Seattle headquarters received a data request from 203.0.113.5 and token asdfqwerzxcvtyuioplkjhgf.,"['Amazon', ""'s"", 'Seattle', 'headquarters', 'received', 'a', 'data', 'request', 'from', '203.0.113.5', 'and', 'token', 'asdfqwerzxcvtyuioplkjhgf', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
11,"On December 12th, 2020, Microsoft Corporation in Redmond used IP 198.51.100.99 for token ytrewqlkjhgfdsamnbvcxzpoi.","['On', 'December', '12th', ',', '2020', ',', 'Microsoft', 'Corporation', 'in', 'Redmond', 'used', 'IP', '198.51.100.99', 'for', 'token', 'ytrewqlkjhgfdsamnbvcxzpoi', '.']","['O', 'B-tim', 'I-tim', 'O', 'I-tim', 'O', 'B-org', 'I-org', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
12,Angela Merkel spoke at the Berlin conference and logged in from 172.16.254.7 using token lkjhgfdsamnbvcxzpoiuytrewq.,"['Angela', 'Merkel', 'spoke', 'at', 'the', 'Berlin', 'conference', 'and', 'logged', 'in', 'from', '172.16.254.7', 'using', 'token', 'lkjhgfdsamnbvcxzpoiuytrewq', '.']","['B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
13,Facebook's Menlo Park office registered access from 2607:f8b0:4005:805::200e with token qazxswedcvfrtgbnhyujmkiolp.,"['Facebook', ""'s"", 'Menlo', 'Park', 'office', 'registered', 'access', 'from', '2607:f8b0:4005:805::200e', 'with', 'token', 'qazxswedcvfrtgbnhyujmkiolp', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
14,Elon Musk tweeted from 203.0.113.45 while using token mnbvcxzlkjhgfdsapoiuytrewq.,"['Elon', 'Musk', 'tweeted', 'from', '203.0.113.45', 'while', 'using', 'token', 'mnbvcxzlkjhgfdsapoiuytrewq', '.']","['B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
15,"The New York Times reported that on 01/01/2023, a login from fe80::a00:27ff:fe4e:66a1 was made with token plmoknijbuhvygctfxrdzeswaq.","['The', 'New', 'York', 'Times', 'reported', 'that', 'on', '01/01/2023', ',', 'a', 'login', 'from', 'fe80::a00:27ff:fe4e:66a1', 'was', 'made', 'with', 'token', 'plmoknijbuhvygctfxrdzeswaq', '.']","['O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
16,IBM's London office accessed 192.0.2.1 on Monday with token jhgfdsamnbvcxzpoiuytrewqlk.,"['IBM', ""'s"", 'London', 'office', 'accessed', '192.0.2.1', 'on', 'Monday', 'with', 'token', 'jhgfdsamnbvcxzpoiuytrewqlk', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
17,"On Friday, the headquarters of OpenAI located in San Francisco logged in from 198.51.100.22 with token qazwsxedcrfvtgbyhnujmikolp.","['On', 'Friday', ',', 'the', 'headquarters', 'of', 'OpenAI', 'located', 'in', 'San', 'Francisco', 'logged', 'in', 'from', '198.51.100.22', 'with', 'token', 'qazwsxedcrfvtgbyhnujmikolp', '.']","['O', 'B-tim', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-org', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
18,Mark Zuckerberg used token plmkoijnuhbygvtfcrdxeszwaq and logged in from IP 10.10.10.10.,"['Mark', 'Zuckerberg', 'used', 'token', 'plmkoijnuhbygvtfcrdxeszwaq', 'and', 'logged', 'in', 'from', 'IP', '10.10.10.10', '.']","['B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O']",True
19,The event held in Tokyo on 2023-05-15 saw attendees connect from 172.217.3.110 with tokens qwerasdfzxcvtyghbnujmiklop and plmoknijbuhvygctfxrdzeswaq.,"['The', 'event', 'held', 'in', 'Tokyo', 'on', '2023-05-15', 'saw', 'attendees', 'connect', 'from', '172.217.3.110', 'with', 'tokens', 'qwerasdfzxcvtyghbnujmiklop', 'and', 'plmoknijbuhvygctfxrdzeswaq', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
20,Angela Merkel received a message from 2001:0db8:85a3::8a2e:0370:7334 and used token qazwsxedcrfvtgbyhnujmikolp.,"['Angela', 'Merkel', 'received', 'a', 'message', 'from', '2001:0db8:85a3::8a2e:0370:7334', 'and', 'used', 'token', 'qazwsxedcrfvtgbyhnujmikolp', '.']","['B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
21,Google's Mountain View campus logged in on 2024-01-01 from IP 192.168.0.101 with token lkjhgfdsamnbvcxzpoiuytrewq.,"['Google', ""'s"", 'Mountain', 'View', 'campus', 'logged', 'in', 'on', '2024-01-01', 'from', 'IP', '192.168.0.101', 'with', 'token', 'lkjhgfdsamnbvcxzpoiuytrewq', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
22,Facebook Inc. in Menlo Park was accessed yesterday via 198.51.100.17 and token mnbvcxzlkjhgfdsapoiuytrewq.,"['Facebook', 'Inc.', 'in', 'Menlo', 'Park', 'was', 'accessed', 'yesterday', 'via', '198.51.100.17', 'and', 'token', 'mnbvcxzlkjhgfdsapoiuytrewq', '.']","['B-org', 'I-org', 'O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'O', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
23,Tesla's CEO Elon Musk logged into the San Francisco server at 172.16.254.9 using token qazwsxedcrfvtgbyhnujmikolp.,"['Tesla', ""'s"", 'CEO', 'Elon', 'Musk', 'logged', 'into', 'the', 'San', 'Francisco', 'server', 'at', '172.16.254.9', 'using', 'token', 'qazwsxedcrfvtgbyhnujmikolp', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'O', 'B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
24,"On Tuesday, Amazon in Seattle initiated a connection from IP 10.1.1.1 using token plmoknijbuhvygctfxrdzeswaq.","['On', 'Tuesday', ',', 'Amazon', 'in', 'Seattle', 'initiated', 'a', 'connection', 'from', 'IP', '10.1.1.1', 'using', 'token', 'plmoknijbuhvygctfxrdzeswaq', '.']","['O', 'B-tim', 'O', 'B-org', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
25,Dr. John Smith from Harvard University accessed the system at 198.51.100.88 with token mnbvcxzlkjhgfdsapoiuytrewq.,"['Dr.', 'John', 'Smith', 'from', 'Harvard', 'University', 'accessed', 'the', 'system', 'at', '198.51.100.88', 'with', 'token', 'mnbvcxzlkjhgfdsapoiuytrewq', '.']","['O', 'B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'B-org', 'I-org', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
26,Microsoft's Redmond campus logged in on 2023-11-11 from 192.168.100.100 using token qazwsxedcrfvtgbyhnujmikolp.,"['Microsoft', ""'s"", 'Redmond', 'campus', 'logged', 'in', 'on', '2023-11-11', 'from', '192.168.100.100', 'using', 'token', 'qazwsxedcrfvtgbyhnujmikolp', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'B-geo', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
27,Elon Musk's Tesla accessed the network from IP 172.217.5.110 using token lkjhgfdsamnbvcxzpoiuytrewq.,"['Elon', 'Musk', ""'s"", 'Tesla', 'accessed', 'the', 'network', 'from', 'IP', '172.217.5.110', 'using', 'token', 'lkjhgfdsamnbvcxzpoiuytrewq', '.']","['B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'B-org', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
28,The conference in San Francisco on 10/10/2023 saw a login from fe80::abcd:1234:5678:9abc with token mnbvcxzlkjhgfdsapoiuytrewq.,"['The', 'conference', 'in', 'San', 'Francisco', 'on', '10/10/2023', 'saw', 'a', 'login', 'from', 'fe80::abcd:1234:5678:9abc', 'with', 'token', 'mnbvcxzlkjhgfdsapoiuytrewq', '.']","['O', 'O', 'O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
29,Facebook's Menlo Park branch accessed 203.0.113.8 on Wednesday with token qazwsxedcrfvtgbyhnujmikolp.,"['Facebook', ""'s"", 'Menlo', 'Park', 'branch', 'accessed', '203.0.113.8', 'on', 'Wednesday', 'with', 'token', 'qazwsxedcrfvtgbyhnujmikolp', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
30,Mark Zuckerberg logged in from IP 192.0.2.55 using token plmoknijbuhvygctfxrdzeswaq on Sunday.,"['Mark', 'Zuckerberg', 'logged', 'in', 'from', 'IP', '192.0.2.55', 'using', 'token', 'plmoknijbuhvygctfxrdzeswaq', 'on', 'Sunday', '.']","['B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O']",True
31,Tesla's San Francisco plant received a command from 198.51.100.45 accompanied by token mnbvcxzlkjhgfdsapoiuytrewq.,"['Tesla', ""'s"", 'San', 'Francisco', 'plant', 'received', 'a', 'command', 'from', '198.51.100.45', 'accompanied', 'by', 'token', 'mnbvcxzlkjhgfdsapoiuytrewq', '.']","['B-org', 'O', 'B-geo', 'I-geo', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O']",True
32,The CEO Elon Musk connected from IP 10.10.10.20 and used token qazxswedcvfrtgbnhyujmkiolp on Friday.,"['The', 'CEO', 'Elon', 'Musk', 'connected', 'from', 'IP', '10.10.10.20', 'and', 'used', 'token', 'qazxswedcvfrtgbnhyujmkiolp', 'on', 'Friday', '.']","['O', 'O', 'B-per', 'I-per', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-IP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'U-Token', 'O', 'B-tim', 'O']",True
